<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="data_export.xslt"?>
<NewDataSet>
	<!--
		https://mssqladmin.secureserver.net/21/scripts/2005/login.aspx
		Database: anamdb
		User Name: anamdb
		Password: W0rri3sTing
		
		New Database: anem
		New User Name: anam
		New Password: W0rri3sAnam!
	-->
	<Table>
		<Id>1</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Elsie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Abbott</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>2</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
		<LastName>Abbott</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>3</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Kasran P.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Abraham</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>4</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Louise "Billie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>A''Dair</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>5</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Nicholas A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Aiello</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>6</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mary</FirstName>
		<LastName>Alarid</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>7</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al</FirstName>
		<LastName>Allen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>8</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Hernandez</FirstName>
		<LastName>Amanda</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>9</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lucille</FirstName>
		<LastName>Anders</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>10</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Janet</FirstName>
		<LastName>Anderson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>11</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Millie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Anderson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>13</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ernest</FirstName>
		<LastName>Andriese</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>14</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Peter</FirstName>
		<LastName>Angeles</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>15</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>R. Senio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Aurujo</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>16</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mildred</FirstName>
		<LastName>Austin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>17</Id>
		<Rank>ADC</Rank>
		<FirstName>John A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bailey</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>John A. Bailey, longtime Oakland resident, born in Wilkes County, North Carolina, went peacefully at the VA Hospital in Palo Alto, Calif., on Monday, August 29, 2005. He is survived by his wife, Mrs. Thelisie Bailey, daughters, Pamela George, Jonna and Lisa Bailey, son-in-law Ernest George, Jr., granddaughters, Kailah and April George, great-grandsons, Khalid and Elijah Threats, sisters, Mrs. Arlene Harper and Mrs. Marjorie Beason of New York. He was a retired Chief Petty Officer and proudly served in the United States Navy for 20 years. After retirement from the Navy, John went to work at NAS Alameda AIMD and retired again as an Engine Mechanic WG-10.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>18</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alfred</FirstName>
		<LastName>Barragan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>19</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Barrone</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>20</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alice M.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Beck</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>21</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>J. H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bertillo</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>22</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>James I.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Birbeck</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>23</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Wilson "Bill"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Black</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>24</Id>
		<Rank>Cmdr.</Rank>
		<FirstName>Robert J.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Blaisdell</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/blaisdell-rj.jpg" width="212" height="288" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDR Blaisdell joined the U.S. Navy in September of 1942. After completing training at various bases, he was designated a Naval Aviator on November 1, 1944, and received his "Wings of Gold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His first duty assignment was to a PBY squadron in Jacksonville, Florida. He saw service in WW2, the Korean War, and the Cuban Missile Crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He served on the USS Essex, USS Bon Homme Richard, USS Ticonderoga, and the USS Forrestal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He flew a wide range of Navy aircraft, from seaplanes to jet attack bombers and jet fighters. He was a member of VAH-2, the first A3D "Skywarrior" squadron to deploy on straight-deck carriers before the introduction of the angled deck design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He concluded his naval career as Operations Officer at NAS Alameda, California, retiring in 1971. He then joined Wells Fargo Bank and became the VP of Real Property Maintenance, retiring after 14 years in 1986.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>25</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Wanda June</FirstName>
		<LastName>Borromeo</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;A resident of Alameda, Wanda was born in Red Oaks, Oklahoma on January 7, 1936 to the late Gus and Ollie Smith of Chowchilla, CA. She passed away peacefully on July 11, 2008 with her family at her side. She is survived by her loving husband, Robert of 51 years. She is also survived by daughters Brenda Piro and Barbara Arbios, Son-in-laws, Vince Piro and Max Arbios, Grandchildren. Frank Piro, Jennifer Piro, Robert Piro, Richard Quinn, Rachel Arbios and Hannah Arbios. She worked as a production controller at NAS, Alameda. She was a devoted and loving wife, mother and grandmother. She will be deeply missed by her family and friends. The family will hold private services per Wanda''s request. In lieu of flowers, donations may be sent to: Sutter VNA Hospice, 1900 Powell St., Suite, 300, Emeryville, CA 94608 Greer Family Mortuary 510-865-3755&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Published in the Bay Area News Group publication on 7/18/2008&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>26</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Walter E.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bosworth</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>27</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
		<LastName>Braunea</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>28</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Clauzell Jr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Briggs</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>29</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert Palmer</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bronken</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/bronken-ap.jpg" width="400" height="508" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Albert Palmer Bronken, age 84, passed away November 25, 2007 in Jacksonville, FL, with his son Gary, daughter in law Frieda, and grandchildren Amanda and Jonathan by his side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Al was born on August 26, 1923 in Madiera Co., California. Al and his wife Myrtle moved to Alameda around 1948 where they resided and worked until, her death in 2000, after which time he moved to Orange Park, Florida to live with his son Gary and daughter in law Frieda Bronken.  Al served in the Navy from 1942 -1945 and worked for the Department of Defense at the Naval Air Rework Facility (NARF), Naval Air Station, Alameda from 2/12/45 to 7/21/76 where he retired as a Quality Assurance Supervisor. Al was a past member of the Alameda Elks Lodge, past president of the Alameda Commuters, and Alameda Golf Association.  Al was the proud grandfather of 9 grandchildren, 12 great grandchildren, and 1 g-great grandchild. Al will be remembered by his family and friends for his great zeal for life, his gentle, giving and caring nature, and his stories of days gone by. &lt;b&gt;He was a terrific husband and wonderful father and grandfather who found great joy and happiness in his family and friends.&lt;/b&gt; Al left an everlasting mark on the hearts of everyone that knew him and will be greatly missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Al will be cremated and his remains transported back to California for burial next to his wife Myrtle at San Joaquin Valley National Cemetery, in Gustine, California. Family and friends will be notified of the date in the near future. Donations in his honor may be made to the University of Mississippi Medical Center, UMMC Fund, Attention: Office of Development, 2500 North State Street, Jackson, Mississippi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by his son, Gary Bronken&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>30</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lois</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brooks</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>31</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brown</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>32</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Clark</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brown</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Clark Brown, who passed away around 2004 or 2005, worked in Bldg 400 3rd deck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--provided by Mr. William E. Glazewski &lt;i&gt;"an Alameda artisan from Bldg 400"&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>34</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jennie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Buford</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>35</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Helen</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bunn</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>36</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Burkhead</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>37</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jess S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Burns</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>38</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ralph</FirstName>
		<LastName>Busby</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>39</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ruth B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Butler</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>40</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Burleson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>41</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Federico</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cabello</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;Mr. Federico Cabello worked in the NARF Hydraulic Department from 1968-1977.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He began working as a mechanic, and was promoted to supervisor. Mr. Cabello passed away in 1977.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/cabello-f.jpg" width="568" height="456" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:568px;"&gt;From left to right: Capt. Wolf, Mr. Epps, &lt;b&gt;Federico Cabello&lt;/b&gt;, W. N. Poindexter&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="clear:both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/cabello-f-details.jpg" width="568" height="420" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="clear:both;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>42</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Maureen L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cammack</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>43</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>James "Jimmy"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Camp</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>44</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Caslin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>45</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Santiago</FirstName>
		<LastName>Caso</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>46</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Castillo</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>47</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Roland</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cecchettini</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>48</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Errol</FirstName>
		<LastName>Celada</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Errol Celada passed away in December 2008.&lt;p style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;Michael Celada is asking for help in contacting people that knew his father.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;He can be reached at 925-997-4155 or &lt;a href="mailto:mike.celada@ranone.com"&gt;mike.celada@ranone.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>49</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Celada</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>50</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Louis</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cerro</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>51</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joseph H. Jr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Chavez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>52</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Janice</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cipresso</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>53</Id>
		<Rank>Cmdr.</Rank>
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Clancy</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/clancy-r-aircraft.jpg" width="412" height="243" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cdr. Robert Clancy was a highly decorated World War II Navy aviator who bombed and helped sink the Japanese super battleship Musashi off the Philippine Islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cdr. Clancy was awarded the Navy Cross, the Navy''s second- highest military decoration, as well as the Silver Star the third-highest) and the Distinguished Flying Cross, for his bravery while flying the famed Helldiver carrier-based dive-bomber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was like thousands of other young men who volunteered for duty right after the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor in December 1941. Cdr. Clancy began training in January 1942 -- prospective flyers were first trained as civilian pilots -- and started training as a military pilot in August of that year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By May 1943, he had received his wings, and after learning how to land on an aircraft carrier, he set sail for Hawaii on the carrier Yorktown in January 1944. He eventually ended up as a lieutenant junior grade on the Intrepid and flew the Curtiss SB2C Helldiver, a fast dive-bomber that would swoop in on an enemy, unload its bombs and streak away. It was not a job for the faint of heart or stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"The hell bombers would go down from 17,000 feet,"&lt;/span&gt;recalled Dan Baker, 84, of Lafayette, and a fellow pilot with Cdr. Clancy on the Intrepid. &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"You''re flying the plane down and the targets were pretty big -- a battleship is about 800 feet long and 125 feet wide, and if you have a clear day it''s almost hard to miss. At about 9,000 feet, there''s a white carpet of anti-aircraft fire. You hope it doesn''t hit you."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baker said that he and Cdr. Clancy and other aviators would zoom down from above and drop their bombs as their accompanying torpedo planes attacked horizontally at sea level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"When you pull out (of the dive bomb run), you “jink” the airplane, skidding the plane up and down so you don''t have a constant target as you''re pulling away,"&lt;/span&gt; Baker said. &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"The battleships are shooting 17-inch guns into the water to create a big splash and try to knock you down. You get by the cruisers, you get by the destroyers, then run like hell and get out of there."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was just the kind of thing Cdr. Clancy went through during the Battle of Leyte Gulf. In January 1945, the Fresno Bee wrote a story about his exploits over the Pacific in October 1944, during the thick of that bitter battle off the Philippines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"While the storm of flak rattled him around in his cockpit,"&lt;/span&gt;the newspaper reported, &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"Clancy picked himself another battleship, pushed the Helldiver straight down and, while his tail gunner gazed straight up past his toes, watching for fighters, got the surface mammoth''s deck in his bombsight, set his flaps to slow him as much as possible and let the bomb go. He was at 1,800 feet when he pulled out of the screaming rush."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"Striking the deck squarely, the armor piercing bomb slammed through and exploded in the battleship''s innards. Clancy''s gunner, looking down and back now as the bomber fought upward, clicked a camera shutter and got pictures of several bombs exploding as they hit the surface craft. The battleship slowed, stopped, floundered and sank."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cdr. Clancy was one of many aviators credited with sinking the huge 65,000- ton battleship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"In this Battle of the Sibuyan Sea,"&lt;/span&gt; according to the &lt;a href="http://www.history.navy.mil/" target="_blank" style="text-decoration:underline;"&gt;Naval Historical Center''s Web site&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;the Musashi "was hit by some 19 torpedoes and 17 bombs. Though her heavy protection withstood this massive damage to a degree probably unsurpassed by any other contemporary warship, Musashi capsized and sank about four hours after she received her last hit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baker said Mr. Clancy was &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"an excellent pilot"&lt;/span&gt; and used to have a favorite reply when somebody called him on the radio and asked where he was. Clancy would radio back, &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"I''m at 35,000 feet, flat on my back and going straight up."&lt;/span&gt; Baker said he thought Clancy may have borrowed the line from a popular novel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the war, Cdr. Clancy returned to California, where he worked in sales for a division of the large medical manufacturing company Johnson &amp; Johnson. He remained in the Naval Reserve, flying out of Alameda Naval Air Station until he retired in 1958, at the rank of Commander.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>54</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Clayton</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>55</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Stacy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Clemons</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>56</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Coffey</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>57</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Betty</FirstName>
		<LastName>Colborn</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>58</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lillian M.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Collier</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>59</Id>
		<Rank>AVCM</Rank>
		<FirstName>Jerry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cook</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/cook-j.jpg" width="369" height="400" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Command Master Chief Jerry T. Cook joined the Navy in 1960 at the age of 20. He went through Boot Camp in San Diego, California and then was selected to attend Aviation Electronic Technician (AT"A") School in Memphis, Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting out as an aviation electronic technician, AT Cook served in numerous squadrons including VA123, VAH2, FAETUPAC and VAQ136 at NAS Whidbey Island in Oak Harbor, Washington; VAW132, VAQ132, NAMTD 1073 (A3), and NARU at NAS Alameda, California; NWC China Lake in China Lake, California; NAS Lajes Field in the Azores, Portugal, and his final duty station, before retirement, in VT21 at NAS Kingsville, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He served on many ships including the USS Independence, USS Kitty Hawk and the USS Enterprise, helping in the rescue efforts during the devastating USS Enterprise fire in 1969. He took great pride in the men he worked with and asked them for their best. They responded, honoring him with a handmade plaque that read "JC’s AT''s - The impossible we do with a smile. Miracles take a little while".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upon retirement at NAS Kingsville after 28 years of service in 1987, he took some time off to travel around the country before settling in Sedro Woolley, Washington where he started a business with his wife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>60</Id>
		<Rank>Captain</Rank>
		<FirstName>Stuart</FirstName>
		<LastName>Corey</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>61</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leticia</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cornell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>62</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>James C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Crump</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>63</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Virgil "Bud"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Crumpacker</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>64</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Irene C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cullen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Irene C. Cullen was born in Pennsylvania on May 31, 1913. At the beginning of World War II, she moved with her mother to Pearl Harbor, and began her lifelong service to our country. From Hawaii, they moved to Alameda, still civil servants. When the U.S. Navy shut down that base, Irene and others assigned there had the opportunity to come to the newly opened Naval Air Station, Lemoore where she served until her retirement.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>65</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Eva</FirstName>
		<LastName>DeLeon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>66</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Salome</FirstName>
		<LastName>DeLeon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>67</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Daly</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>68</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Davis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>69</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Davis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>70</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ed</FirstName>
		<LastName>DeCosta</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Ed DeCosta passed away this morning (Oct 18, 2008) peacefully after suffering from Leukemia. His wife Rita and family was at his side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was living in El Cajon with daughter Ann &amp;amp; husband Bob, with services and interment in a veteran cemetery in that area &amp;amp; not in Northern California where he leaves another daughter Beth &amp;amp; husband Jack and son Edward.&lt;/p&gt;He worked many happy years at Naval Rework Facility Alameda lastly with the 300 Engineering Department, and leaves many sad friends.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>71</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert "Al"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dewitt</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>72</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Daniel J. Sr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dixon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>73</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Isaiah</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dixon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>74</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leslie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Donnelly</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>75</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Don</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dugan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Nov. 24, 1928 - Dec. 2, 2008 Dad passed away December 2, 2008, surrounded by his loving family. He was preceded in death by his loving wife of 23 years, Mary, who he sorely missed. Now they are together again. He is survived by his loving children Linda and Jeff Stone, Cindy Dugan, David Dugan, Don Dugan, Doug Burkett, Nancy and Rich Harry, Sherri Sheehan and his loving grandchildren Nikki Stone, Scott Stone, Sgt. David Boreliz, Candis Sheehan and Stacey Sheehan.&lt;p style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;Also survived by his dear sister Joan Vratarich of Pennsylvania, his extended family and many dear friends. Dad was born in Pennsylvania and settled in California after serving in the Navy. He worked for the Naval Air Station in Alameda, CA, until his retirement. Dad loved sports of all kind, especially football and baseball, and of course, golf. Dad was an avid golfer, golfing twice a week until he fell ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;He will be greatly missed by his family and friends. Visitation will be held, Thursday, December 11, 2008 from 4:30 to 8:30pm at the Chapel of the Chimes, 32992 Mission Blvd., Hayward. A Chapel Service will be held on Friday, December 12, 2008 at 10:00am. Chapel of the Chimes, Hayward (510) 471-3363&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Carol Fairweather&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>76</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Steven Lowell</FirstName>
		<LastName>Edde</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Steven Lowell Edde a longtime San Anselmo resident and former NADEP Alameda employee, passed away peacefully on January 20th, 2008 in the presence of his loving family at St. John''s Hospital in Santa Monica following a spirited battle with sarcoma cancer. Born on January 25, 1947 in Stockton, Steve moved to San Rafael when he was nine years old. Steve graduated from Terra Linda High School in 1964, attended College of Marin, obtained a BS in Industrial Engineering at the University of California at Berkeley in 1969, and received his MS degree in Systems Management.&lt;p&gt;Steve is survived by Kathleen, his childhood neighbor, high school sweetheart and wife of 39 years, his children Holly of San Rafael, and Michael of San Francisco, his mother Mickey of San Rafael, sister Leta of Cameron Park and his mother-in-law Jacqueline Fields of San Rafael. He is preceded in death by his father Lowell (Hap) Edde and his father-in-law Alfred (Dee) Fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve had a larger than life presence and was passionate about things dear to his heart. He loved family, friends, cooking, outdoor adventures, music, and sports.  Steve''s enthusiasm for living life to its fullest was felt by those around him and he will be greatly missed at all of the annual events which he organized for family and friends each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve worked as an Industrial Engineer for the US Navy at the Alameda Naval Air Station for 33 years. After the base closure in 1997, he switched roles and became an Environmental Engineer, managing base cleanup and transfer. In 2003, Steve retired from the Navy with 39 years of service and went to work for Innovative Technical Solutions, Inc. to serve as the company''s liaison to Navy Projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Susan Neishi&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>77</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
		<LastName>Edwards</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>79</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jesus</FirstName>
		<LastName>Falcon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>80</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Fee passed away in early January 2007.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>81</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Felker</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>82</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Glen</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fernandez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>83</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alice</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fick</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>84</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fikaris</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>85</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Dorothea Barrone</FirstName>
		<LastName>Finley</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>86</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Eliseo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Flores</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>87</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Steve</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fooshee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Steve Fooshee passed away July 30, 2008 in La Pine, Oregan. A memorial service will be held at Grissom''s San Lorenzo Chapel, on August 8, 2008, at 11:00am, with reception immediately following at 16167 Via Lupine in San Lorenzo.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>88</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Louise</FirstName>
		<LastName>Fyvie</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Laura Louise Fyvie passed away on November 7, 2007. Laura started working at Naval Air Station in Alameda, CA and was transferred to the Naval Base in San Diego, CA upon their closing. She worked 16 years until receiving a medical retirement.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>89</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Claire</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gaddi</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>90</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Gene</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gaeta</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Gene Gaeta was stationed at NAS Alameda in the early to mid 80''s, and passed in early 2008.  He detailed the Hornet that''s downstairs in our museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--provided by Mr. Ron Beets&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>91</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Amador</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garcia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>92</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Genaro</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garcia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>93</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Nick</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garcia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>94</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alfredo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garza</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>95</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garza</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>96</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gay</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>97</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Clara R.</FirstName>
		<LastName>George</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>98</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry</FirstName>
		<LastName>George</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>99</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Evangelina "Vangie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gerado</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gerado-e.jpg" width="268" height="382" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>100</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gillard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>101</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Chris</FirstName>
		<LastName>Goddard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>102</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gonzalez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>103</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Sabas</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gonzalez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>104</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William "Bill"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Goodsell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. William "Bill" Goodsell passed away on November 4, 2008 at the age of 90. Born in Salt Lake City, Utah on January 16, 1918, Bill came to California with his wife and new family in 1941. He immediately started work at the Alameda Naval Air Station as an electrician and worked there until his retirement in 1973. He was a longtime member of the Island Masonic Lodge No. 215 and also a member of the Sons In Retirement, Isle City Branch, No. 60. Bill was preceded in death by his loving wife of 61 years, Ann Goodsell in 2001. He is survived by daughters Sharon (Ed) Raney of San Leandro, Doris (Bob) Curlett of San Leandro and sons Leland (Verna) Roberts of San Leandro and Kenneth (Patty) Roberts of Hawaii. He is also survived by 9 grandchildren, 23 great grandchildren and 5 great great grandchildren.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>105</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ernest</FirstName>
		<LastName>Goulart</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>106</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Stanley Melvin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Guido</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Stanley Melvin Guido, 83, of Roseburg, Oregon, passed away Saturday, July 26, 2008, at his home.  He was born May 3, 1925 in Oakland, California, to Manuel and Sophie (Bonita) Guido.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Guido served in the U.S. Army during WWII. In 1944 in Oakland, California, he married Geraldine Gonsalves.  Stanley worked for 30 and retired as a superintendent with the U.S. Government. He was a member of the AARL Radio Club, Superintendent''s Association, DAV and VFW. In 1991, Geraldine and Stanley moved from San Leandro, California, to Roseburg, Oregon. While he was able, Stanley attended St. Joseph Catholic Church. Survivors include his wife, Geraldine Guido of Roseburg, Oregon; daughter, Joanne Erickson and her husband, Mike of Albany, Oregon; son, Melvin Guido and his wife, Debie of Gold Beach, Oregon; granddaughter/daughter, Keely Bettencourt and her husband, who was like a son Tim; grandson, Craig Hall; granddaughter, Lori Hall and grandson, Darren Hall; great grandchildren, Tiffany Bettencourt; Donald Bettencourt and Roxanne Bettencourt; brother-in-law, Ivy Morris and numerous nieces and nephews. Stanley was preceded in death by his parents, Manuel and Sophie and a sister, Geraldine Morris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funeral services will be held on Wednesday July 30, 2008, at 11 a.m. at Wilson''s Chapel of the Roses. Military honors provided by the VFW District 12 Honor Guard will follow within the grounds of Roseburg Memorial Gardens. In lieu of flowers the family requests that contributions be made in Mr. Guido''s memory to Douglas Hospice 500 SE Cass suite 260, Roseburg, OR. 97470.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;From the August 1, 2008 edition of  the Roseburg Oregon "News Review"&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>107</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joseph Anton</FirstName>
		<LastName>Haefele</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>March 5, 1913 - August 10, 2008 Resident of San Leandro Joseph Anton Haefele, age 95, died peacefully at his home surrounded by his family. He was preceded in death by his parents Joseph A. and Anna K. Haefele, and his sister, Florence Mella. Joseph was born in San Leandro and lived there his entire life. He was employed by United Airlines and the Alameda Naval Air Station for 32 years. He is survived by his wife Marie; son Joseph (June) Haefele; daughter Kitty Bartee; and grandchildren Lisa, Eric and Mee Bartee. Funeral Services were private. He will be missed by his family and friends. HOLY ANGELS FUNERAL &amp;amp; CREMATION CENTER FD-#1456 510-537-6600</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>108</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Harrison</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/harrison-b.jpg" width="288" height="377" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:288px;"&gt;January 2, 1943 - January 6, 2005&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;He moved to Castro Valley in 1957 where he attended Castro Valley High School and graduated in 1960. Bob went to San Jose State College prior to joining the US Army in 1962. He received his honorable discharge as a Sergeant in 1965, and returned to college. In 1966, Bob went to work for the Naval Air Station Alameda. Bob worked there for 25 years and retired as a Production Superintendent in 1991. He was best known for his love of golf, fishing, and classic cars. After retirement he opened a golf club repair shop known as Bob''s Birdie Shop. Bob was a resident of Walnut Creek since 1968. He was a member of the Walnut Creek Chapter of the Elks Lodge and the Dukes Classic Car Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>109</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Carol</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hayes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>110</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alice</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hickey</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/hickey-a.jpg" width="430" height="327" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:430px;"&gt;Alice Norma Hickey - January 24, 1925 - April 1, 2008&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alice lived in Alameda all her life and worked at NAS Alameda in Disbursement for 43 years. She enjoyed meeting with her NAS coworkers at Tim''s restauarant on Webster Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>111</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Walter "Bert"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Higgins</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>112</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hoffman</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>113</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Victor L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Howard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>114</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hudson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Bill Hudson worked in Building 167 the Propeller Shop.&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Henry Faulkner&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>115</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>David</FirstName>
		<LastName>Huerta</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>116</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
		<LastName>Huerta</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>117</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Dave</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hull</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>118</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jackson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>119</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Carl W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jackson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>120</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charlie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jackson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Charlie Jackson worked in Building 167 the Propeller Shop.&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Henry Faulkner&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>121</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joe</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jackson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>122</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
		<LastName>James</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Joseph James worked in Building 167 the Propeller Shop.&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Henry Faulkner&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>123</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Elizabeth</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jencks</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Elizabeth Jencks and her husband George A. Smoot both served as Naval Aviation Machinist mates at NAS Alameda during World War II.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>124</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Kathryn H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jessen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>125</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jiles</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>126</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Herman W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johansen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>127</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alvin S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>128</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Barabara E,</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>129</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Johnson worked as an engineering tech in NADEP Alameda 300 department, and passed away within a couple of years after the base closure.&lt;p&gt;--provided by Mr. Paul H. Degenkolb&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>130</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Melvin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnston</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Melvin Johnston Resident of San Pablo Died peacefully 4/12/08. Survived by wife Joanne, sons Peter, David, Michael &amp;amp; their wives, 7 grandchildren, and 3 great-grandchildren.&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--Published in the Contra Costa Times on 4/19/2008.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>131</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Edward R.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnstone</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>132</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jose</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>133</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles E.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kennedy</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>134</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kopter</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/kopter-f.jpg" width="448" height="344" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:448px;"&gt;NADEP Alameda&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>135</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Michael Henry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Krouse</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Henry Krouse was born July 26, 1922 in Columbus Grove, Ohio.  In 1942 he joined the Navy to train as a pilot determined to fly in the aftermath of the attack on Pearl Harbor. He was eventually assigned to a torpedo-bomber crew on board the USS Enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Oct. 25, 1944, he and his wing man spotted a Japanese battleship while flying 20,000 feet over the ocean north of Leyte Gulf in the Philippines then swooped down just a few feet above the waves to fire torpedoes that severely damaged the ship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"Undaunted by intense enemy anti-aircraft fire ... Krouse pressed home vigorous attacks,"&lt;/span&gt; his Navy Cross citation reads. &lt;span class="narrative"&gt;"His courage, expert airmanship and unwavering devotion to duty contributed to the success of his squadron in fulfilling this dangerous mission."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The week before the Battle for Leyte Gulf, Krouse and his crew survived a night at sea in life rafts when they were forced to ditch their plane because it was running low on fuel on the return from a mission in Manila Bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Never wounded in combat, he amassed many medals for valor in World War II and the Korean War, including the Distinguished Flying Cross and seven Air Medals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He later served as an executive officer and flight instructor for a training squadron and headed an aircraft maintenance unit at Alameda Naval Air Station,  He retired as a Lieutenant Commander in 1963.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>136</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Iria H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Large</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>137</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Benjamin Ero</FirstName>
		<LastName>Laxamana</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>139</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Webster</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>140</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jim</FirstName>
		<LastName>Leonard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>141</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Leonhardt</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>142</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John "Jack"</FirstName>
		<LastName>LeStrange</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>143</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Erma B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Le Sueur</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>144</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lieser</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>145</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Henri</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lindhurst</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>146</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Walter Lee</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lindsey</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Lindsey was a NARF employee at Alameda Naval Air Station for 35 years, 1944 - 1980. He passed away in Aug. 2000.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>147</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ellen</FirstName>
		<LastName>Link</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>148</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lisanti</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>149</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Peter Renaldo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Locarnini</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Peter Renaldo Locarnini of San Leandro Passed on July 19, 2008 at 86 years of age due to advanced dementia. He was a career military man, serving as Chief Petty Officer, for 25 years in the US Navy and 14 years at the Naval Air Rework Facility in Alameda, CA. He enlisted in the Navy in 1939 and was stationed in the Philippines when the war broke out with Japan. In May 1942, he was captured and became a prisoner of war. For the next three and one-half years, he was interned in a POW camp at Mukden, Manchuria. After the liberation and his return to the United State, he re-enlisted in the Navy and spent the next 20 years serving his country all around the world.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>150</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lomas</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;"My Dad was a sheet medal worker.  He had special security clearance during the Vietnam war and was stationed for 9 months in Saigon Vietnam, Okinawa, NAS Clark base in the Philippines, Lemore NAS, and El Toro NAS.  He Retired after 35 years with the government."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Velma Lomas&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>151</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Erasmo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lozano</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>152</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Florence B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lundy</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>153</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George Francis "Blackie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lunge</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;h2&gt;17 December 1914 to 10 November 2005&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;My Father was a Civilian Employee of NAS ALAMEDA, working as an Electrician in the Power House from 18 March 1946 until he retired on 28 September 1972. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Stephen Lunge&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>154</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Maguire</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>155</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Melvin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Malfatti</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>156</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mona</FirstName>
		<LastName>Marsh</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>157</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles "Doc"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Martin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Martin was one of the earliest Comptrollers at NAS Alameda, having transferred there prior to its commission from Moffatt Field and earlier, Lakehurst, NJ.  Mr. Martin was also a plank-owner.&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by his granddaughter Annie Mockabee&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>158</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ron</FirstName>
		<LastName>Martin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>159</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Martinez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>160</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Luciano</FirstName>
		<LastName>Marroquin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>161</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Trellis</FirstName>
		<LastName>Massey</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Trellis Massey, who passed away in April 2006 at age 95, was retired from NARF (NADEP 94114) where he worked in the Avionics Division Building 400 Shop 94114.&lt;p&gt;He was a WWII Veteran who fought in Africa and earned 2 Bronze Stars.  He retired from the Air Force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Massey was also a trained watch maker.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>162</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mata</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>163</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Walter W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Maynes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>164</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Arthur "Archie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>McGuire</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Long time NAS SUPPLY Director, Arthur "Archie" McGuire passed away mid November 2006.  Archie is sorely missed by his Golfing Buddies. &lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. K. Johnston&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>165</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lawrence J.</FirstName>
		<LastName>McClintock</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>166</Id>
		<Rank>Lt. Cmdr.</Rank>
		<FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
		<LastName>McMahon</LastName>
		<Status>USN</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/mcmahon-b.jpg" width="200" height="220" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. McMahon was a Lieutenant Commander with &lt;a href="/units/aircraft/va-304.aspx" style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;VA-304&lt;/a&gt;. He was a Bombardier Navigator onboard the A-6E Intruder.  He died on 5 April 1994.  Lieutenant Commander Rand McNally was also killed during the accident. &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Sean McMahon&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>168</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alfred A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Medeiros</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>169</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jerome "Babe"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Medeiros</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>170</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Trinidad</FirstName>
		<LastName>Medina</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>171</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jay Alan</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mensch</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Jay Alan Mensch of Huber Heights, Ohio, passed away on Saturday September 20, 2008 at the age of 61. Private services were held at North Chapel.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>172</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Sam</FirstName>
		<LastName>Metcalf</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Sam Metcalf, retired supervisor for the hydraulic shop in building 5, died Wednesday March 15, 2007 in Memphis, Tenn. &lt;i&gt;--provided by Carol Fairweather&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>173</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Donald</FirstName>
		<LastName>Metts</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>174</Id>
		<Rank>RADM</Rank>
		<FirstName>Stanley J</FirstName>
		<LastName>Michael</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/michael-sj.jpg" width="217" height="300" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A native of Cincinatti, Ohio, Rear Admiral Michael was appomited to the U.S. Naval Acadamy in 1916. He graduated in 1919.&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After service in battleships and destroyers, he completed flight training and was designated a Naval Aviator in 1925. During World War II, he commanded the seaplane tenders, Matagorda and Golsborough, The escort carrier Nassau and the light carrier Cabot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rear Admiral Michael participated in the battle for Tarawa, Guam, Saipan, Truk, Phillipine Sea and Leyte Gulf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was twice awarded the nation''s second highest decoration, the Navy Cross, for heroism while in command of the USS Cabot. Promoted to Commodore in 1945, he served as Commanding Officer of NAS Alameda and Commander of air bases in Northern California until 1948. He retired from the Navy as a Rear Admiral in 1949.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>175</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Larry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Miguel</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>176</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Milbauer</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Frank Milbauer, passed away March 22, 2008 at the Emanuel Medical Center, Turlock, CA.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>177</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>L.F.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>178</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>M. Helen</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>179</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Thomas Lloyd</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mockabee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/mockabee-tl.jpg" width="300" height="241 alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:300px;"&gt;Mr. Mockabee at his desk&lt;br /&gt;at NAS Alameda in 1956&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Mockabee joined the navy at age 24, was stationed at NAS when it was first commissioned, and is a plank-owner. It was there that he met and married my mother, Josephine Cecelia Martin, a clerk, and the daughter of the first NAS Comptroller &lt;a href="/InMemory.aspx?id=157" style="text-decoration:underline;"&gt;"Doc" Martin&lt;/a&gt;. My father was stationed at Moffitt Field during WWII, where he was on active duty in the Navy, and an engineer on one of the "lighter-than-air" blimp crews that patrolled the coast of N. California.  Following the War they returned to Alameda where my father worked as a civilian at NAS Alameda. He was the Comptroller at the time of his death in 1958.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by his daughter Annie Mockabee&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>180</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Money</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>181</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Montano</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Frank Montano, who passed away around 2000, worked in Bldg 400 3rd deck.&lt;p&gt;--provided by Mr. William E. Glazewski &lt;i&gt;"an Alameda artisan from Bldg 400"&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>182</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lovell "Lowell"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Moore</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>183</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Oscar</FirstName>
		<LastName>Moraida</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>184</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Elizabeth S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Murphy</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>185</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Gus</FirstName>
		<LastName>Muzio</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>186</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Navarrete</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Frank Navarrete who retired as Captain in the NAS Fire Dept, died 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Dale Navarrete, Retired NADEP 1994&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>187</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Nelson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>188</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marty</FirstName>
		<LastName>Newton</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>189</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Nils</FirstName>
		<LastName>Nilsson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Nilsson was a planner for the S-3 program, and passed away on April 7, 2008.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>190</Id>
		<Rank>Lt. Cmdr.</Rank>
		<FirstName>Richard M.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Nixon</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/nixon-rm.jpg" width="112" height="161" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:112px;"&gt;Lieutenant Commander Richard Nixon of the United States Navy, 1945&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Lt. Cmdr. Richard M. Nixon passed away at Cornell University Hospital, New York, on April 22nd, 1994 having served with distinction in the Pacific war during WW II. During late 1944 and early 1945 and, after over-seas duty, he served as Administrative Officer at ALAMEDA NAVAL AIR STATION. (see page 62, Richard M. Nixon by Conrad Black.) He later served as Congressman for the 12th District of California, U.S. Senator, Vice President and President of the United States. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Mr. William O.
			DeWitt&lt;/i&gt;&lt;ul style="float:left; list-style-position:inside;"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Nixon" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Nixon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.history.navy.mil/faqs/faq60-8.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Naval Historical Center - Transcript of Naval Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>191</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leo G.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Noakes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>192</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Manuel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>193</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Owens</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>194</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Wm. G. "Bill"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Paasch</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Wm. G. "Bill" Paasch, AOM, passed away on 9-12-07 at age 82 in Louisville KY.&lt;p&gt;Bill served during WWII (circa 1945-46) at NAS Alameda with CASU-6 under Chief AOM''S
			"Dix" Dixon and Arkie Camp.&lt;br /&gt;Our hanger was the most NW''ly on the aerial shot of the base under construction.&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img width="320" height="200" style="cursor: pointer;" onclick="window.location.href=''Gallery.aspx''" alt="" src="/Images/Gallery/NAS/nas-jan-42.jpg" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;NAS Alameda under construction.&lt;br /&gt;-- photo taken in January 1942.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style="clear: left;"&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Wm. O. "Stretch" DeWitt AOM(ret) CASU-6&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>195</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Emmett</FirstName>
		<LastName>Parker</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>196</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Cornette</FirstName>
		<LastName>Partee-Hoston</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/hoston-cp.jpg" width="291" height="600" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:291px;"&gt;NADEP Alameda - 420 Division&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>197</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
		<LastName>Paugh</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>198</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alfredo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Perez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba, and Ellie Perez&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>199</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Gabriel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Perez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba, and Ellie Perez&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>200</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Rene</FirstName>
		<LastName>Perez</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba, and Ellie Perez&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>201</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Agnes F.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Peters</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>202</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Anna</FirstName>
		<LastName>Polizzi</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>203</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leon</FirstName>
		<LastName>Pon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Leon Pon was a WWII veteran, a training sergeant with the US Army Air Corp 8th Tactical Reconnaisance Squadron stationed at Stuttgart, ARK.  After WWII ended, he returned to the Bay Area to work at NAS Alameda, where he met his future wife, Emma, who was one of the "Rosie the Riveter" working there after the war effort.  Eventually he became an Electronic System Inspector, QA at NARF, located in Bldg 400, A-53.  He retired in 1970. He encouraged his sons to consider the military; e.g. I was with Fleet Hospital Support Office, USN, until it was the last Alameda command BRACed a decade ago. He passed away on the same day as the "Fall of Saigon" in 2008. "Fair winds and following seas" as he soars into the wild blue yonder &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Robert Pon&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>204</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>"Pinky"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Purvis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>205</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rankin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>206</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ed</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ranson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>207</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alan John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rasczewski</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Alan died suddenly at his home in Columbia City, Oregon on August 12, 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan was born and raised in Fremont CA. He graduated from Irvington High School in 1978. Alan worked for many years at the Alameda Naval Air Station and then moved to Columbia City , Oregon. He worked as a superintendent for the Army Corp of Engineers in Portland Oregon. Alan loved his work and all of the people he worked with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan was adored by all who met him and will be missed greatly by his family, friends and coworkers. Alan was full of life and always had a story to tell. He was the life of the party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan leaves behind his wife Brenda, son Micheal and daughter Courtney Rasczewski of Columbia City Oregon. His father Edward Rasczewski of Fremont and close friend Geraldine Borges of of San Leandro,Ca. He also leaves behind his sister Debbie Hooberman and Brother in law Peter Hooberman of Piedmont CA, nieces Lindsay, Amy, Lauren and nephew Adam Hooberman. Also his sister Julie Salvador and nephew Daniel and Christopher Salvador all of Caldwell, Idaho. Alan was prededed in death by his mother Madelyn Maciel Rasczewski. He also leaves behind several extended family members, friends and co-workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A celebration of Alan''s life was held at the home of Larry &amp; Margie Dino in Livermore, on August 16,2008. In lieu of flowers, a memeorial college fund for Alan''s children is in the process of being set up. For further information on the celebration of Alan''s life or the memorial college fund for Alan''s children please contact Larry or Margie Dino (510)304-0914 or &lt;a
			href="mailto:Margie.dino@comcast.net" style="text-decoration:underline;"&gt;Margie.dino@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>208</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert "Al"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ravina</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>209</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert H. Sr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Reed</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>210</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Thomas R.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Reed</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>211</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Resendes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>212</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Quincy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rhodes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>213</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Margaret</FirstName>
		<LastName>Richards</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>214</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Pearl</FirstName>
		<LastName>Richards</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>215</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Dick</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rieder</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>216</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Luther</FirstName>
		<LastName>Roberts</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>217</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George</FirstName>
		<LastName>Robertson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/robertson-g.jpg" width="234" height="374" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;NADEP Alameda&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>218</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>James Stephen</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ryan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/ryan-js.jpg" width="193" height="277" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:193px;"&gt;James Stephen Ryan&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Born: 10/09/1942&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Died: 04/13/2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitation: Wednesday, April 16, 2008 - 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Funeral Service: Thursday, April 17, 2008 - 11:00 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interment: Benton Cemetery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p style="clear:both;"&gt;James Stephen Ryan, age 65, of Benton, KY, died Sunday, April 13, 2008, at Centennial Hospital in Nashville, TN. He was a member of the Hardin Baptist Church. He was a retired planner and estimator for Naval Air Station in Alameda, CA and a member of the National Association of Retired Federal Employees. He was a veteran of the U.S. Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funeral service will be at Collier Funeral Chapel at 11:00 AM, Thursday, April 17, 2008, Rev. Ricky Cunningham officiating. Friends may call after 5:00 p.m. on Wednesday. Interment will be at Benton Cemetery, Benton, KY.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.collierfuneralhome.com:80/index.cfm?fuseaction=web.viewobit&amp;obitid=1836" style="text-decoration:underline;" target="_blank"&gt;Collier Funeral Home Obituary&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>219</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Donald A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Santisteban</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>220</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ann</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sather</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>222</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Justine C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Scaramuzzino</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>223</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Wilhelm L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Schanzenbacher</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>224</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Warren</FirstName>
		<LastName>Schilling</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>225</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Clyde</FirstName>
		<LastName>Schmidt</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>226</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lillian T.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Schmidt</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>228</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>April</FirstName>
		<LastName>Scott</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>229</Id>
		<Rank>Cmdr.</Rank>
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Shannon</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Robert Shannon, Cdr. USN Ret. served at NAS Alameda in 1968 - 1969. It was his last active duty station before he retired from 31 years active duty. He then worked in Civil Service as the Education Services Officer until 1984.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>230</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Albert W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sharron</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>231</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Isabel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Simmons</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>232</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ed</FirstName>
		<LastName>Smith</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Smith, worked in the NADEP Instrument Shop in Building 400.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>233</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Smoot</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Smoot and his wife Elizabeth (nee Jencks) both served as Naval Aviation Machinist mates at NAS Alameda during World War II.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>234</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Rita</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sonquest</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>235</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Stanford</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/stanford-r.jpg" width="448" height="344" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;NADEP Alameda&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>236</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Emil</FirstName>
		<LastName>Stutz</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>237</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert J.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sutton</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>238</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
		<LastName>Swiger</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>239</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joe Jr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tapia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>240</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Manuel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tapia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>241</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Matthew "Matt"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Telles</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>242</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Eddy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Thompson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>244</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mary "Terry"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tijerina</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>245</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tomblin</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>246</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leandro</FirstName>
		<LastName>Torres</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>A former employee of NAS Corpus Christi, Texas who was transferred to NAS Alameda, California in 1959. &lt;i&gt;-- provided by Gino Leyba&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>247</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Betsy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Trevethan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>248</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Oliver</FirstName>
		<LastName>Valerio</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Valerio served in the U.S. army during WWII from March 1941 - January 1946 and he was employed for many years as an Aircraft Mechanic General with the Naval Air Station, beginning in February of 1946 - October of 1949 (his supervisors were William Scmelzer and E. Hall) , then again from August of 1950-through the 1960s (his supervisor was Jack Blunt).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oliver Valerio received his pilot''s license from Esteban Flying School in Oakland in the 1930''s, was a member of the American Motorcycle club, and was one of the first men to cross the Bay Bridge on his Indian motorcycle when the bridge first opened.  While enlisted in the U.S. army, as 1st Sargent, he led one of the first Philippine Battalions while serving in the Pacific during WWII under his birthname, Eustaquio O. Valerio.  Oliver later became a career Aircraft Mechanic and was the founding president of Rizal Post 598, a Women''s Auxiliary of the American Legion, raising twelve children on the island of Alameda (7 boys and 5 girls) with his wife, Carmen, until he passed on June 11, 1969, exactly 30 years to the day after a historical photo of him was taken at the SF Bay Airdrome on June 11, 1939.  Oliver Valerio, his wife and children were featured on the front page of the Alameda Times Star in March of 1966, under the headline, "Meet a King-Sized Alameda Family" (stored on microfiche at the public library).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by his daughter, Rosalie A. Valerio&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>249</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bettye</FirstName>
		<LastName>Vaughan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>250</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
		<LastName>Vita</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>251</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Viola M.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Violette</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/violette-vm.jpg" width="200" height="315" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;My mother, Viola M. Violette was a Navy Wave (2nd graduating class, I believe) who for a time was stationed at Alameda Naval Air Station, CA as a Storekeeper. I believe she was in the service during WWII from 1944 to 1945/6. She was originally from Yakima, Washington. She passed away on Feb. 14, 2001 in Yakima and had a military burial. She was just shy of 90 years old. She was always proud of her service in the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by her son, David F. Schauf&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style="clear: both; margin-top: 1em;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/gallery/waves/2nd-wave-class-II-lg.jpg" width="750" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;Group II of the 2nd WAVE graduating class of 1944 from Midgeville, GA.&lt;br /&gt;My Mother, Viola Violette, is 2nd from right in the bottom row of the picture.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="clear: both; margin-top: 1em;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/gallery/waves/aircraft-mat-office-1944-lg.jpg" width="750" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;Group photo taken on the 2nd anniversary of the Aircraft Material Office September 29th, 1944.&lt;br /&gt;My Mother, Viola Violette, is fourth from the left in the 2nd row from the bottom.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="clear: both; margin-top: 1em;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/gallery/waves/violette-vm-letter.jpg" width="750" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="clear: both; margin-top: 1em;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>252</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Orvis T.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wade</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/wade-ot.jpg" width="250" height="339" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			Orvis was from St. Augustine, Texas. He enlisted in the U.S. Navy in 1953 and spent 30 years in the Navy advancing to Master Chief Petty Officer Store Keeper. After retiring from the Navy in 1983, he went to work in the 700 Department at the Naval Aviation Depot Alameda from 1985 to 1993. He transferred to North Island HSLWINGPAC, San Diego in 1993 due to the Alameda base closure. He performed as an IMRL Manager/Equipment Specialist until his death in October 2003.&lt;p&gt;Mr. Wade was one of the first "Special Assistants for Minority Affairs" in the US Navy.  This can be verified by reviewing the All Hands Magazine from April 1971, PG-18.  He was stationed at Norfolk at the time. I worked with Mr. Wade at COMHSLWINGPAC from 2000 until his death in 2003.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by &lt;a href="mailto:michael.g.cook2@navy.mil"&gt;AFCM(AW) Michael G. Cook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>253</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
		<LastName>Waggener</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>254</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lena M. "Babe"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wagner</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>255</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ray</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wallace</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Wallace was an engineer at NADEP on temporary assignment (3 years) during the late 80s in the Philippines when he passed away.&lt;p&gt;--provided by Mr. Paul H. Degenkolb&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>256</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Myrtle</FirstName>
		<LastName>Washburn</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>257</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lileon</FirstName>
		<LastName>Webb</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>258</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Rodney</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wilcoxson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>259</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
		<LastName>Williams</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;h2&gt;June 7, 1935 - June 17, 2008&lt;/h2&gt;Resident of Moraga Tony F. Williams died Tuesday, June 17, 2008 after a brief illness. He was born in Moultrie Georgia, he served 4 years in the United States Air Force. Mr. Williams worked at Amtrak retiring after 49 years. He also worked at Alameda Naval Air Station. Retiring after 33 years of service. He was an active member of the Improved Benevolent Protective Order of Elks of the World. Mr. Williams leaves to mourn his wife Lemette, daughters Pamela Williams, Eliah Bell, Son Marc Williams, and stp daughter Monica Coleman. 7 grandchildren and 2 step grandchildren, 2 brothers and 3 sisters. In addition, he leaves behind Elector Williams and an extended family of aunts, uncles, sister-in-law, brothers-in-law, cousins, nieces, nephews, lodge brothers, sisters and friends who will miss him dearly.&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- published in the Bay Area News Group publication on 6/29/2008&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been told that Tony Williams passed away on June 17th. He was a supervisor in bldg 530. I met Tony in 1978 in Norfolk, Va. while I was working in the Sidewinder missile shop. He was part of a workload transition team from Alameda. Sometime after that, a decision was made not to move the Sidewinder shop from Norfolk to Alameda. I spent the next two years trying to get a job in Alameda. Finally in August of 1980, I got the job and Tony was my supervisor. I was assigned to the Sparrow assembly area. Tony could be tough sometimes to work for. One day he called me to his desk and really got to me. So I went back to my work area and was cussing him out to my co-worker. Then from behind a locker, I heard Tony say "The shadow knows". We both laughed. Tony lived in Moraga, drove a Mercedes, wore nice suits, and smoked cigars. He would stand there sometimes with his cigar and say "I''m just a poor strugl''in minority", so he could watch the expressions on peoples faces. After I got in the apprentice program, I worked for Tony again for three months. He treated me with respect and gave me praise on my evaluation. The last time I saw Tony was at the Amtrak station in Oakland where he worked part time. We didn''t always get along, but I liked Tony and I am really sad to hear he is gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by &lt;a href="mailto:alvinaman@gmail.com"&gt;Alvin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>260</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Martin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wilson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>261</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marlene</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wolf</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>262</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Younger</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr. Younger was assigned to NAS Alameda 1942 as a CPO, as a civilian, he was an Instrument Tech, Production Controller &amp; Supervisor. Retired as Production Planning and Control Division Director in 1979.
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Mr. Ken Younger&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>263</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joe</FirstName>
		<LastName>Zboyovsky</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>264</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charlie T.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Andrews</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Andrews was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in July 26, 2006.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>265</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Cliff</FirstName>
		<LastName>Archibald</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Archibald was a Machinist at NAS Alameda.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>266</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Henry</FirstName>
		<LastName>Arcieri</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Arcieri was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 1991.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>267</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Pete A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Armato</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Armato was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 20, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>268</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jack W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Baker</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Baker was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 1, 1998.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>269</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Melvin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bellmer</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Bellmer was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in December 9, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>270</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Tom</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bice</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Bice was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 24, 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>271</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bim</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Bim was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 1989.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>272</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jim W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Blackstock</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Blackstock was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in November 7, 1999.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>273</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John F.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brossard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Brossard was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 5, 2001.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>274</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brum</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Al was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in February 26, 1990.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>275</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Buck</FirstName>
		<LastName>Buchignani</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Buchignani was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 7, 1993.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>276</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Buendia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Buendia was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in May 5, 2006.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>277</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jim</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bussel</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Bussel was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1997.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>278</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marvyn</FirstName>
		<LastName>Chinn</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Chinn was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 22, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>279</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul I.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Combs</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Combs was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in October 11, 2000.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>280</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ciurana</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Ciurana was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 29, 2008.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>281</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Irvin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Flynn</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Flynn was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 3, 1989.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>282</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Doel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Frazier</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Frazier was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in December 13, 1995.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>283</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>LaVerne</FirstName>
		<LastName>Frisbee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Frisbee was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in January 5, 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>284</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gaillard</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Gaillard was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April, 24, 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>285</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John F.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garcia</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Garcia was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in December 30, 2001.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>286</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ray</FirstName>
		<LastName>Garavatti</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Garavatti was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in July 15, 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>287</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joe</FirstName>
		<LastName>Henry</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Henry was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 2000.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>288</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Sherman</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hensley</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Hensley was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in December 3, 1995.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>289</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Howell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Howell was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 1989.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>290</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hunt</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Hunt was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1995.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>291</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kapellas</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Kapellas was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 6, 1999.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>292</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kent</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Kent was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>293</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Arthur</FirstName>
		<LastName>Krapp</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Krapp was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 2006.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>294</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kriletich</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Kriletich was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in July 23, 2001.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>295</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kremper</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Kremper was a Machinist at NAS Alameda.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>296</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Langedam</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Langedam was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>297</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leroy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lampton</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Lampton was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in November 4, 1997.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>298</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill "Ping"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Lee was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 20, 2008.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>299</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Everett E.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Liborio</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Liborio was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in January 5, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>300</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Henri</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lindhurst</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Lindhurst was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 12, 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>301</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
		<LastName>Luis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Luis was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1999.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>302</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
		<LastName>McNamara</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. McNamara was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in November 30, 1998.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>303</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leland</FirstName>
		<LastName>Merrick</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Merrick was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 12, 1999.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>304</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mignone</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Carl was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1990.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>305</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
		<LastName>Milbauer</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Milbauer was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 21, 2008.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>306</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al</FirstName>
		<LastName>Miraglio</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Miraglio was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>307</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ted</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mock</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Mock was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 30, 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>308</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Arthur Roy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Muller</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Muller was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in October 5, 1997.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>309</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John J.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Nordman</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Nordman was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 9, 2001.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>310</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Richard D.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Parke</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Parke was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in July 24, 2005.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>311</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Pederson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Pederson was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>312</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Nick S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Perusina</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Perusina was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 20, 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>313</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rasmussen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Rasmussen was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 1996.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>314</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rego</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Rego was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 1, 2006.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>315</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joe</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rose</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Rose was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 2, 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>316</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Al</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sadler</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Sadler was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in February 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>317</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ken</FirstName>
		<LastName>Seiz</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Seiz was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in January 19, 2007.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>318</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Spurgeon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Spurgeon was a Machinist at NAS Alameda.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>319</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Schagrue</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Schagrue was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away on November 8, 1986.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>320</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
		<LastName>Scobee</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Scobee was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in August 4, 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>321</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Weldon</FirstName>
		<LastName>Smith</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Smith was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 8, 1998.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>322</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Souza</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Souza was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 6, 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>323</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Hershel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Stephens</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Stephens was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 27, 2004.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>324</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charlie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Stone</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Stone was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in March 1997.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>325</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Morris D.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Thompson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Thompson was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in May 22, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>326</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ustasouski</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Ustasouski was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in July 29, 1991.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>327</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ray</FirstName>
		<LastName>Valent</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Valent was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in November 1989.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>328</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Vittori</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Vittori was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in December 1990.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>329</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Doug</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wardell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Wardell was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in May 30, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>330</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harry M.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Weed</LastName>
		<Status>Jr.</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Weed was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in October 12, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>331</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles G.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wilson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Wilson was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in October 16, 2002.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>332</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bill</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wright</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Wright was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in September 1988.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>333</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Takeshi</FirstName>
		<LastName>Yanagi</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Yanagi was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in April 17, 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>334</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Varney</FirstName>
		<LastName>Yuen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Yuen was a Machinist at NAS Alameda, and passed away in 2003.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Russ Drake, organizer of the NAS Alameda Machinist Luncheon Group&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>335</Id>
		<Rank>RADM</Rank>
		<FirstName>Ray</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hemmings</LastName>
		<Status>USN (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>Mr. Raymond Hemmings, a Menlo Park resident, passed away on January 1, 2001 following a brief illness. He was 81.&lt;p&gt;A San Mateo native, he graduated from Stanford University and Stanford Business School, and did advanced study at the Harvard School of Business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Hemming joined the U.S. Navy as a commissioned officer following the attack on Pearl Harbor. At the end of the war, he maintained his commission in the U.S. naval reserve and retired after 37 years of service with the rank of rear admiral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a longtime member of the Association of Naval Aviation, the Tailhook Association and the Navy League. In recent years he was a member of the Aircraft Carrier Hornet Advisory Board on the U.S.S. Carl Vinson committee. His association with the Navy was one of the great passions of his life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1958, Mr. Hemming established a private accounting practice in San Mateo that became, in partnership with Edwin Morse, Hemming Morse Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was known for his philanthropy, and gave ongoing support to the College of San Mateo, Stanford University and the U.S. Navy, and was on the advisory board of the Alameda Naval Air museum.&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>336</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alice</FirstName>
		<LastName>Elliott</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;My grandmother, Alice Elliott worked at Alameda Naval base during World War II. I am still trying to find out more information from my family but I know that one of the jobs she had was to go through clothes that had been shipped back from over seas. In fact, she once found a real foot in a boot. I also think she may have shot rivets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Dina Nave&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>337</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Deward</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gresham</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Deward Gresham passed away in December 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gresham-d-card.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Mr. William T. Larkins&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>338</Id>
		<Rank>MSgt.</Rank>
		<FirstName>James W.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Selter</LastName>
		<Status>USAF (Ret.)</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;James W. Selter was born February 25, 1938 in Boston, Massachusetts and passed away February 11, 2009 at his home in Sheridan, California at the age of 70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;James was preceded in death by his mother Rebecca (Scott) Marion; father George Selter; brothers Charles and Richard. James is survived by his wife of 50 years, Janeth; four sons: James (Susan) Selter, George (Heidi) Selter, Bruce (Angie) Selter, Scott (Elizabeth) Selter; 11 grandchildren: Christine (Osha) Meisel, Theresa (Charles) Hanks, Eric, Adam, John, Joseph, Sierra, Sean, Sabrina, and Shane Selter; 1 great-grandchild, Wyatt Meisel; two sisters, Elaine Bumpus, of Redmond, Washington and Dorothy Brown of Connecticut, two brothers Robert Selter of Hedgesville, Virginia and Robert Marion of Bridgewater, Massachusetts; and numerous nieces and nephews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;James served in the United States Air Force for 27 years as an Aircraft Electrical Systems Specialist. James was stationed abroad in the Azores and numerous bases throughout South East Asia, as well as McGuire AFB, New Jersey, Kincheloe AFB, Michigan, Beale AFB, California and McClellan AFB, California where he retired in 1985. James also served in the Civil Service as a Quality Inspector at NAS Alameda, California and NAS Jacksonville, Florida, retiring in 2000. James was very active in Little League, Youth Football and Boy Scouts of America in the Wheatland and Lincoln areas. James was a member of Disabled American Veterans and active in 2951st CLSS Alumni''s Group at McClellan AFB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since retirement, James and Janeth have enjoyed traveling and visiting relatives throughout the United States and Canada. Services will be held at Valley Chapel Beale AFB, on February 16th, at 1:00 p.m. Private interment will be at Sacramento Valley VA National Cemetery in Dixon, California at a later date. In lieu of flowers please send remembrances to the American Heart Association, 1710 Gilbreth Road, Burlingame, California, 94010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can sign the on-line Guest Book at: &lt;a href="http://www.legacy.com/SacBee/GB/GuestbookView.aspx?PersonId=124136288" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;http://www.legacy.com/SacBee/GB/GuestbookView.aspx?PersonId=124136288&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>339</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Gertrude B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ternes</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/Images/InMemory/ternes-gb.jpg" width="300" height="299" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption" style="width:300px;"&gt;Gertrude B. Ternes worked in the Public Works Department, Administrative Division in the 1960s.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>340</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Inez</FirstName>
		<LastName>DeVincentis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>341</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marjorie "Margie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Herrera</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Born 20 November 1924, Passed away on 25 November 2008.  She was a production control supervisor in Bldg 5.
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>342</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>David D.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sillers</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;David D. Sillers (Jan. 12, 1949 - Apr. 7, 2009) worked in Production Control on the 3rd deck of Bldg 400.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;David D. Sillers died peacefully on April 7, 2009 in Alameda''s Bay View Nursing &amp; Rehab Center. Dave was born on January 12, 1949 and was a long-time resident of Alameda, graduating from Alameda High School in 1967.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;At AHS Dave will be remembered as the only student who received a spontaneous burst of applause at graduation, starting with the 471 graduates, and welling up until everyone in the auditorium was clapping and cheering. It was a sincere tribute by his fellow graduates to a student for an achievement that did not appear on the printed listing of scholastic accomplishments. It was the student recognition -- unrehearsed and unorganized -- of something they thought was pretty wonderful. The applause kept growing as Dave accepted his diploma. The hand clapping continued as he climbed down the stairs from the stage, and it did not stop until Dave walked up the aisle and returned to his seat. The story behind the student admiration of Dave began three years earlier in 1964 when, as a popular freshman athlete, he was fighting for his life after an accident that left him severely paralyzed. Determined to let nothing stop him, he applied himself to a home study program outlined by his teachers. Eventually he was able to use a wheel chair. Then, he was able to walk -- very slowly at first, and then with a limp. Gradually he learned to re-use his arms and hands and eventually he began to attend classes on a part-time basis and then finally after more than a year, he became a regular student at AHS once again.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;So, when he received his diploma that graduation night 43 years ago, it was like running a kick-off back for the winning touchdown, hitting a grand slam home run in the final inning, or scoring the winning basket in the sudden-death overtime. The heart-warming hand clapping of his 471 fellow students, their families and friends meant much more than the wild cheering of the biggest rooting section. Dave, who might have been one of Alameda High''s great athletes if things had been different, proved he already had what high school sports are supposed to teach - courage, determination, and strength.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;The things he learned at AHS followed Dave through the rest of his life in Alameda. Dave continued to grow and be involved in things beyond just himself. Dave went to San Francisco State University, graduating with a bachelor''s of arts degree in 1974. Soon after college Dave joined and then became an officer of the Alameda JayCee''s where he met some of his life long friends. He was appointed as a commissioner for the Alameda Parks &amp; Recreation District serving for many years. Dave was well known and did outstanding service work for Alameda and as a result was selected as one of the "Outstanding Young Men of America." For the past six years Dave has been living in Alameda''s Bay View Nursing &amp; Rehab Center, since in 2002, he was hit by a car while crossing the street in a crosswalk near his home. This second accident left Dave completely bed-bound as he was nearly completely paralyzed except for his head and right arm.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Dave''s mother and father were an incredible support to him during his entire lifetime. They were an integral part of Dave''s adult life as he was included in all their activities, parties and trips. However, his mother, Wilhelmine Sillers, passed away two years ago and his father, CDR. Colin B. Sillers, USN (ret''d), passed away 4 months ago. Dave greatly missed both his parents after their passing, especially his Dad as he was the person who visited Dave every single day while he lived at Bay View Nursing &amp; Rehab Center. Dave is survived by his brother, Bruce (Coby) Sillers, Jr. of Atlanta, GA, his nephew, Doug Sillers of Santa Barbara, CA and his niece, Katy Sillers Krippaehne of Tacoma, WA.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>343</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Murphree</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr. Murphree, who passed away on April 4, 2009, was a former S-3 Planning supervisor at NADEP Alameda.

		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>344</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Barbara Perrin MacKenzie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gingrich</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Barbara died peacefully in her sleep with her children at her side, on June 4th, 2009. She was 78. Family and friends are invited to join her children and their families in a Celebration of Life to be held at Greer Family Mortuary, 2694 Blanding Ave., off Fruitvale, in Alameda on Saturday, June 27th at 1:00 pm. A reception will follow the services at the Sandpiper Complex in San Leandro off Marina Blvd., and Washington Blvd (parking is limited so park on street and walk-in). Directions will be provided at the Mortuary. Flowers are welcome, as Barbara was the quintessential Gardener. However, as a member of the "Best Friends" animal society and with the caring help of Hospice, any donation of your personal discretion is respectfully appreciated. For further information, please call: Greer Family Mortuary (510)
			865-3755.
			&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Barbara''s obituary can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.legacy.com/obituaries/insidebayarea/obituary.aspx?page=lifestory&amp;pid=128395536" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.legacy.com/obituaries/insidebayarea/obituary.aspx?page=lifestory&amp;pid=128395536&lt;/a&gt;
			where you also can sign the guest book.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Barbara''s nephew Doug DeLong provided this information. Barbara was a truly sweet woman who enjoyed life. I
			enjoyed working with her in NADEP''s Employee Development Division. -- Carol Fairweather&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>345</Id>
		<Rank>Lt. Commander,</Rank>
		<FirstName>Roland Theodore</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ingels</LastName>
		<Status>Jr.</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>Lt. Commander, Roland Theodore Ingels, Jr. (Ted) passed away on December 13, 1998.  He served at NAS Alameda, and was honorably discharged in 1965. -- provided by his daughter Lisa Ingels-Ayala</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>346</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William (Bill)</FirstName>
		<LastName>West</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>347</Id>
		<Rank>Petty Officer</Rank>
		<FirstName>George F.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Batchelor</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			My late father Petty Officer George F. Batchelor was stationed at NAS Alameda for the duration of WWII.  He was an Aviation Metal Smith 1st class. He passed away on May 12, 1998. My father always had fond memories of Alameda and stories of his time of service to our country and would be proud to be added to the memorial page.
			-- provided by Darrell Batchelor
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>348</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Howard C.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Randall</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			My father, Howard C. Randall, was a Plank Owner - his name is on that bronze plaque at the base - and worked there until his death in 1960. He was part of the original survey crew and stayed on working in the Public Works Department.
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by K. Sharon Randall Van Heuit&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>349</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George "Obie"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Oberhart</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			A former employee of NARF/NADEP Alameda, passed away around 1995 or 1996.
			&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			-- provided by Maya Herbert, a fellow NARF/NADEP employee from 1981 - 1993
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>350</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Gerald</FirstName>
		<LastName>Swanson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			A former employee of NARF/NADEP Alameda, was later transferred to NADEP San Diego.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			-- provided by Maya Herbert, a fellow NARF/NADEP employee from 1981 - 1993
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>351</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hesky</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr. Hesky passed away on December 2, 2009.  He was the Hamilton Standard Representative for many years in the Propeller Shop.  Building 167.

			-- provided by Mr. Henry Faulkner
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>352</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Nahm</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;From John Tapia, we have word that former San Leandro City Councilman Paul Nahm has passed away.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Paul Nahm was born in Alameda County in the 1940 and raised in San Leandro. Nahm was active in city and county politics and also worked at the Alameda Naval Air Station. Nahm became active early in the movement to oppose base closures in Alameda County.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;In the early 1990s he went to work for Alameda County as an advocate for workers who would lose their jobs due to base closures. He then became the first executive director of the Oakland Base Reuse Authority which presided over bases in the Oakland-Alameda area that were destined for closure, including the Oakland Army Base.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>353</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert Placy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Beal</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/beal_r.jpg" width="118" height="166" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;On May 9, 1933 in Oakland, CA, Robert Placy Beal was born to the proud parents William and Delores Beal.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Robert attended Berkeley and Oakland Public Schools and graduated from Oakland Technical High School in 1951. Thirty-three years ago Robert married Alice Dinkins. There were no children born to this union. Robert was formerly married to Marguerite Williams-Beal. This union was blessed with two children, a son Robert and a daughter Rhenda.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He loved traveling and meeting new people, horse racing, baseball, bowling and umpiring softball.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Robert departed this life on February 24, 2010, and was preceded in death by his father William Beal, Sr. and
			a sister Barbara Jean Jones.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Robert retired as Supervisor Aircraft Production Control From the Naval Aviation Depot at Alameda, CA. after 37 ½ years of service.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Robert leaves to cherish his memory: his loving and devoted wife Alice Beal, his dedicated and caring mother Delores McCloud, two brothers William Beal, Jr and Fred Beal, sister Mary Louise Jackson, his son Robert, daughter Rhenda, his grandson Keith and step-children: Saeeda Bates, Lytenia Grimes, Maurice Grimes, Marcus Grimes, and grand-daughter Raynisha Spencer.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Also, cherishing his memory are his special circle of friends, a host of nieces, nephews, relatives and other friends, too numerous to name.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Visitation was 4:30 to 8:30 pm on Thursday, Mar. 4th 2010 at The Chapel of Chimes, 32992 Mission Blvd, Hayward, CA. A Memorial Service was held on Friday, Mar. 5th at 10 AM (same place).&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>354</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Mike and Kathi</FirstName>
		<LastName>Greco</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;It is my understanding that Mike and Kathi Greco died as a result of an auto accident in late August 2009.  Their daughter, Jennifer (Greco) Santos, passed along the info.  I first met Kathi as she was in the A-3 hangar with three children hanging on as her husband Mike was returning from a deployment in the "Whale".  Mike was a registered member of the A-3 Skywarrior Association, and both attended the fifty year reunion in 2002 at Van Nuys, CA.  Preston Reynolds of the Bay area may have more details.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by CAPT Bill Young, USN(Ret) &amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#112;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#097;&amp;#119;&amp;#107;&amp;#064;&amp;#119;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#100;&amp;#098;&amp;#101;&amp;#121;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#116;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>355</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bauer</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;In 1989 my brother, William S. Bauer, was stationed at the Alameda NAS and was killed in a naval helicopter crash ("crash" really isn''t the right word-as far as I know the helicopter exploded in mid-air) during a training exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Mr. Steve Bauer&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>356</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Alvin Choy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lum</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Alvin Choy Lum Resident of Fremont Alvin Choy Lum''s (75) courageous battle with lung cancer has ended. He went to peaceful rest at 1045AM on May 28 with beloved family and friends at his bedside. He was born on October 1, 1933 near Canton, China.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Educated as an architect from Tulane University, he spent a majority of his established career at Montgomery Wards in Oakland, CA. He retired from the Naval Repair Facility in Alameda, CA in 1998. In 2003, Alvin and wife Sula retired to Chandler, AZ to be near their son Anthony. During his retirement, he and Sula enjoyed traveling, embarking on many cruises and trips to China.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He is survived by Sula, son Anthony, daughter-in-law Sonya, granddaughter Kenna, brothers Howard and Calvin, sisters Yuk-Moi Owyang and Yee-Lam Yim and numerous nieces and nephews. Visitation at 130PM followed by Memorial Service at 230PM on Saturday, June 6 at Green Acres Mortuary and Cemetery, 401 N. Hayden Road, Scottsdale, AZ 85257.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>357</Id>
		<Rank>RAdm</Rank>
		<FirstName>James</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ferris</LastName>
		<Status>USN</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;While stationed at NAS Alameda between July 1967 to June 1972, James Ferris was commanding officer of the aircraft carrier USS Coral Sea (CV-43). After being promoted to Rear Admiral, Admiral Ferris commanded carrier division three and COMFAIR Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=" http://www.christianmemorials.com/tributes/james-ferris/" target="_blank"&gt; http://www.christianmemorials.com/tributes/james-ferris/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Jim Ferris (former civilian employee for NARDAC San Francisco )&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>358</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Stanwood L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Anderson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;My grandfather served during WWII at NAS.  His name was Stanwood L. Anderson, Sr. he was a Storekeeper.  My grandfather passed away on 11/10/1985.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;A funny story about him:  His mother once asked him what a storekeeper did.  He told her that when the Marines have to go in and take a beach, the storekeepers go in first to set up the concession stands.  He actually had her going for awhile.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Margie Anderson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>359</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Donna Izatt</FirstName>
		<LastName>Keeth</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Donna Izatt Keeth Feb. 6, 1939 - Apr. 22, 2009 Resident of Fremont Donna Izatt Keeth born February 6, 1939 went home on April 22, 2009. Longtime resident of Fremont she retired from Alameda Naval Air Station after 25+ years service. Her family was her world and her friends her treasure, outgoing and vivacious her presence will be deeply missed. Donna was the loving wife of Edgar Eugene Keeth and loving mother to sons Ken, Gary and Gregg and daughters Toni and Desiree; devoted Nana of Josalyn, Kenny, Jessica, Michael, Brian, Monet, Ethan, Gavin, Michaela, Wanda, Ian, Jon, William, and Gillian. Services will be held Friday, May 1, 2009 at the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints, 42500 Gatewood St. in Fremont at 12:00 p.m. Donations may be made in lieu of flowers to the American Lung Association or Stanford University.&lt;p&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>360</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Tom</FirstName>
		<LastName>Palatino</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Palatino was a veteran of WWII and dedicated employee of NADEP Alameda working as a Plane Captain on Oscar 8 (08) Flight test.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Randy Wilson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>361</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Freddie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Voellinger</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Voellinger was a veteran of WWII and dedicated employee of NADEP Alameda working as a Plane Captain on Oscar 8 (08) Flight test.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;--provided by Mr. Randy Wilson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>362</Id>
		<Rank>Lt. (jg)</Rank>
		<FirstName>Roy David</FirstName>
		<LastName>Varner Jr.</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/varner-rd.jpg" width="139" height="175" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the night of March 18, 1959, Lt. Varner died as a result of an aircraft accident at Alameda Naval Air Station, California.  Behind him remains a history of a man, devoted to his country, his family, and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usma57.org/Memorial_Articles.htm" target="_blank"&gt;West Point Class of ''57&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usma57.org/MemorialArticles/VarnerRD.htm" target="_blank"&gt;West Point Class of ''57 Memorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>363</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName />
		<LastName />
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>364</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lula</FirstName>
		<LastName>Taylor-Gamble</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>Lula Taylor-Gamble passed way suddenly (Heart Attack) on October 17, 2009. Lula worked at NADEP as a Quality Assurance Specialist on the S3 aircraft line. She later transferred to SUPSHIP (San Francisco) where she retired in April 1993. She served with the Army Reserve and was a member of the Women Wac Core, FRA (Navy) and DAV. She leaves to mourn her husband Walter Gamble, three sisters and five brothers.</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>365</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Millie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bean</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mildred Ross was born In Sacramento, CA on January 30, 1934. After
			graduating from Sacramento High School, she started working for the
			governement as a secretary. Millie wore a red dress to a friend''s
			party and caught the eye of young Air Force officer Richard "Dick"
			Bean. They married and began a 20-year-long military career. They were
			stationed in Long Island, NY; Pope AFB in North Carolina; and Clark
			AFB in the Phillippines. They enjoyed travelling to Singapore,
			Bangkok, Saudi Arabia, India, Spain, and Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;When Dick retired as an Air Force colonel, Millie and Dick Bean
			settled in Walnut Creek filling their dream home with treasures from
			the world travels. While working full-time, Millie graduated Cum Laude
			with a BA from the University of San Francisco and embarked on a
			career with the Navy at NAS Alameda. After 27 years, Millie retired in
			1996 as a GM-13 Performance Review Division Head. Millie was the
			recipient of the highest honor given to a civilian, the Meritorious
			Civilian Service Award.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;After retirement, still displaying that joie de vivre that Millie was
			known for, Millie and Dick enjoyed post-retirement travel to France,
			Italy, China, Turkey, and Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Millie claimed as her proudest achievement her three children: son
			Tony, and daughters Kimberly and Laurie. She was a devoted and loving
			grandmother to Aaron and Ashley Perry, Rachel Adams, Racquel Bean, and
			Eric Adams.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Millie departed this life on May 27, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>366</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Patricia</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wartenbe</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>367</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Dorothy</FirstName>
		<LastName>McHugh</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Dorothy (Dot) McHugh, 67 Resident of Auburn, CA Born in Falkville AL,
			on 10/21/1942, passed away July 3, 2010 at her home in Auburn, CA with
			her husband of 33 years, Donald McHugh by her side.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Dot was a retiree from Alameda Naval Air Station.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;She enjoyed camping and vacationing with her partner in life (husband)
			Don. She enjoyed spending time with her family and her beloved dogs.
			Dot was a loving &amp; devoted wife, sister, aunt, &amp; grandmother. She will
			be greatly missed by her family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Dot was preceded in death by her mother, Elsie Hooten, father, Carl
			Hooten, &amp; brother, Steven Hooten. She is survived by her husband,
			Donald McHugh, 3 step children, Don H. McHugh, Mary Smits, &amp; Michael
			McHugh, grandchildren, Ronnie, Trent, Sean, Morgan &amp; Mallory, brother,
			Bo Hooten and his wife Lynne Hooten, sisters &amp; their spouses, Barbara
			&amp; Ron Richter, Dolores &amp; Bruce Starr, &amp; 10 nieces &amp; nephews.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;At Dot''s request there will be no public services. Condolences may be
			sent to, 12885 Net Ln., Auburn, CA 95603. Donations may be made to the
			American Cancer Society .&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>368</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Daniel Paul</FirstName>
		<LastName>Baustian</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;On July 18, 1988 my husband, Daniel Paul Baustian, was killed in a MH-53E helicopter crash (explosion) also known as Hurricane 6; He left behind his wife Helene Baustian and daughter Stephanie Baustian, who turned 1 month old that very day.  Rest in peace my love!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Helene Baustian&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>369</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Hermin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Chapman</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Chapman passed away about 5 years ago. He retired in I think South Carolina. He worked in the I think calibration lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Tom Smith who worked on the A-3, P-3 line in the 80''s&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>370</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Herman</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kleinmaus</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/Kleinmaus-h.jpg" width="47" height="66" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr. Kleinmaus was an airplane mechanic at NAS Alameda for many years (over 20 at least) &amp; retired in the late 70''s.&lt;p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;-- provided by his daughter Joan Kellner&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>371</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wong</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;John Wong, who worked in the Pattern/Layout Shop, passed away last
			Thursday, June 10th in a care home at Livermore, California.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Services were held at the Chapel of the Chimes on Piedmont Ave. in
			Piedmont, (Oakland) CA.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Visitation was from from 6-8 PM Friday Evening, June 18th, 2010.
			Funeral services were in the chapel on Saturday, June 19th, 2010.
			Internment was at the Mountain View Cemetery in Piedmont
			(Oakland), CA.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Pete Lew&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>372</Id>
		<Rank>Captain</Rank>
		<FirstName>Edgar E.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Stebbins</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/stebbins-edgar-e.jpg" width="522" height="627" alt="" /&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;Capt. Edgar E. Stebbins and his wife Patsy&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class="clear" style="margin-top:2em;"&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Commander Fleet Air Alameda 1966 &lt;a href="http://www.history.navy.mil/sqdhist/vrc/vrc-30/1966.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.history.navy.mil/sqdhist/vrc/vrc-30/1966.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Commanding Officer USS Boxer CV-21 DEC 1960 - FEB 1962 &lt;a href="http://www.ussboxer.com/USS_Boxer_History.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ussboxer.com/USS_Boxer_History.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Commanding Officer VA-54 1943 &lt;a href="http://www.history.navy.mil/download/va-54-56.pdf" target="b=_blank"&gt;http://www.history.navy.mil/download/va-54-56.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;WW-II Ace &lt;a href="http://www.aerofiles.com/acesww2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aerofiles.com/acesww2.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>373</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William</FirstName>
		<LastName>Howell</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			William A. Howell Aug. 20, 1950 ~ April 1, 2010.

			Resident of Livermore, survived by wife, Ginger; son, Daniel and daughter, Brenda.

			Bill Howell worked in the Standards Lab. He passed away with a stroke.
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>374</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Earl Joseph</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bowling</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Earl Joseph Bowling 1907-1987
			&lt;ul&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Navy (Officer rating)&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;1st Tour 1941 to 1946&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;2nd Tour (exact dates unkown)&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Served during WWII at NAS Alameda and during VietNam.&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Brief employment following first NAVY tour as civilan NARF employee.&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;/ul&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>375</Id>
		<Rank>Capt.</Rank>
		<FirstName>D. A. "Duke"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Campbell</LastName>
		<Status>USN</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/campbell-da.jpg" width="214" height="238" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Captain D.A. ("Duke") Campbell, U.S.N. passed away at the age of 96 on October 22, 2010.  He joined the U.S. Naval Reserve in 1937.  Upon graduation from flight training in Pensacola in 1938, he joined Patrol Squadron 1 in San Diego.  Duke was selected for transfer to the regular Navy in 1940.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Captain Campbell was a highly-decorated pilot during World War II, earning a Distinguished Flying Cross, the Air Medal, an OBE (Order of the British Empire), and several Commendations from the U.S. Navy.  He received the prestigious Order of Merit signed by French President Charles de Gaulle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was Commanding Officer of the U.S. Naval Air Station (NAS) at Alameda, CA.  As the Commanding Officer of NAS Alameda, he inaugurated a series of community-oriented service collaborations between the Navy and the City of Alameda, including working closely with the Mayor and other civic organizations, for which he was presented with the official Seal of the City of Alameda in gratitude for his pioneering efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>376</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lathe</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr. Lathe, who passed away in 2008, worked in the LOX Shop Hanger 11.
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Mr. John Tapia&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>377</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Harold</FirstName>
		<LastName>Pye</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr. Harold Pye worked at NADEP from 1964-1984.
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Denise Pye Swanson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>378</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName> Catherine B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Pye</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mrs. Catherine B. Pye worked at NADEP from 1964-1984.
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Denise Pye Swanson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>379</Id>
		<Rank>StM1c</Rank>
		<FirstName>Johnnie</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tucker</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;My grandfather Johnnie Tucker StM1c served in the Navy from 10 Dec.1943 to 11 Jan. 1946&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Co. Number 2348, Serial or file no:831 60 20.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Vessels and stations served (NAD, NYMI CA): (CASU, Fort Ord, CA); and (NAS in Alameda, CA).&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;W.E Martin Captain, USNR, Commanding is typed on his honorable discharge award.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Rena'' (Tucker) Ivey&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>380</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Henry (Harry)</FirstName>
		<LastName>Theis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/theis-h.jpg" width="120" height="112" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Henry (Harry) Theis, Jr. June 18, 1945 - Dec. 6, 2010 Resident of San Leandro Henry (Harry) Theis, Jr. went to his eternal rest at home on December 6, 2010, at the age of 65. Henry was a beloved Husband, Father, Grandfather, Uncle, Brother, Brother-In-Law as well as a great friend to all who knew him. He was the son of Harry and Genevieve (Hempel) Theis, Sr.. Henry was born on June 18, 1945 in Lake City, FL, but moved to Alameda County, CA when he was 3 months old. He attended Alameda High School in Alameda, CA graduating in June 1962. In January 1964 he joined the United States Navy and served for 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;During that time he met, his future wife Charlotte Amsler on a blind date. They were married at her home in Wentlings Corners, PA. on October 17, 1964, by her father John Martin Amsler. They were married for 46 years. After 30 years of service he retired from the Naval Air Station Alameda. He spent the rest of his retirement spending time with his family and friends, traveling with his wife and doing volunteer work at John Muir Middle School.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He is survived by his wife Charlotte, son Henry III and his wife Janine Malone, as well as his daughter Charlotte, Jr. and her husband Darrin Wheeler and their two children Granddaughter Madison and Grandson Chase. He is also survived by his Grandson Brandon Theis of the United States Army and his wife Morgan Lindstrom. Preceding him in death is his Granddaughter Sabrina Theis. He is survived by four brothers, Michael Theis, NC, Mark Theis, AZ, Kevin Theis, CA, and Kurt Theis, CO and one surviving sister Kristina Reynolds, CA. Preceding him in death are two sisters, Audrey (Lynnda) Carey, CA and Leslee Jaykins, CA and one brother Stephen Theis, CA. He is also survived by many Brother-In-Laws, Sister-In-Laws, Nephews and Nieces. He was deeply loved by all that knew him.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;


		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>381</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jem S</FirstName>
		<LastName>Louie</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/louie-js.jpg" width="197" height="243" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jem S Louie was born in China and grew up in Sacramento. He joined the Army as a young man, serving in Germany, where he developed his taste for German food. Settling in the Bay Area after his service, he married. He and Donna had two sons, Ken and Jeff.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jem spent his Navy civilian career at Naval Air Station Alameda (Naval Air Rework Facility/ Naval Aviation Depot), where he completed a four year apprenticeship program in aircraft electronics, becoming a Journeyman Electronics Mechanic in the Avionics Division and later an Electronics Technician in the Engineering Department. Jem was good at puzzle-solving (as evidenced by those crossword puzzles) and he was an accomplished electronics mechanic.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jem liked a range of music - except for country/ western – and attended many concerts with his friends. An excellent photographer until his eyesight failed, Jem was proudest of the photos he took of his two grandchildren. And what a cook – Jem could always be counted on for a tasty lasagna. He had a wide range of interests. Rarely did Jem say no when asked to a movie/ meal/ walk/ play/ concert/party/ museum.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jem was a quiet man. Those of us who were able to hear his soft voice are grateful for his challenging conversations and wry observations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Provided by Carol Fairweather&lt;/i&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>382</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George B.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hope</LastName>
		<Status>USN Ret.</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Hope who passed away on April 11, 2011, served as an HMC AW/FMF in &lt;a href="http://www.alamedanavalairmuseum.org/units/aircraft/va-303.aspx"&gt;VA-303&lt;/a&gt; from 1978-1981.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;Provided by his son, Mr. Jon G. Hope&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>383</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Sheila D.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Chambers</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Sheila D. Chambers passed away on 2/10. She was a sheetmetal mechanic at hangar 11 shop 95823. Sheila was very talented, It was an honor having her on my crew and having her as my friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Provided by Tim Owyang work leader shop 95823&lt;/i&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>384</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Edmund Cedric</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ryan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Edmund Cedric Ryan passed away peacefully on March 29, 2011. Mr. Ryan worked at NARF on the sheet metal line in B-5 in the 80-90’s.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Edmund was 86 years old. He is survived by his son Edmund E. Ryan and his daughters Jean Syth and Jane Rounsaville. He had 10 grandchildren and 5 great-grandchildren. &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;Provided by Carol Fairweather&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>385</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ellis Dee</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jagger</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Ellis Dee Jagger, 81, of Grass Valley, died Tuesday, Feb. 23. 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Jagger was born May 6, 1928, in Port Angeles, Wash., to Ellis E. and Grace Gillespie Jagger.  He served for 20 years in the U.S. Navy and retired as a chief petty officer. He later retired after more than 20 years from civil service (electronics mechanic at Naval Aviation Depot, NAS Alameda) He was a member of Veterans of Foreign Wars and SIRS. &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Jagger is survived by his sister, Nedra, of Marysville, Wash., and brothers, Robert of Sequim, Wash., and Craig, of Chehalis, Wash. &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;He is preceded in death by his wife, Dorothy Jagger; and his three sisters, Betty, Carroll, and Grace. &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;Provided by Carol Fairweather and Al Renfro&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>386</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>George Edward</FirstName>
		<LastName>White</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. White who passed away in June of 1980, was 60 years old and served in World War II
			and the Korean War, in the Army Air Corp. as a specialized air plane mechanic. He
			worked at Alameda Air Station as civilian in the Navy, as a specialized Air Plane Mechanic,
			who was deployed to Lemore CA, San Diego CA, Widby Island WA.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;Provided by his daughter, Ms. Catherine D. White&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>387</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>David Darwin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Davis</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/davis-d.jpg" width="400" height="184" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Darwin Davis Mar. 21, 1933 - Feb. 14, 2011 Resident of Concord Dave died peacefully at home surrounded by loved ones after a prolonged battle with cancer. Born and raised in Utica N.Y.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He joined the Navy in 1950 and served on the USS Badger and the USS Compton during the Korean conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He married Jean E. Watson of Newport, Rhode Island in 1952. In 1964, Dave and Jean settled in Concord, CA, where they raised four of their six children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave worked for the Naval Air Rework Facility at the Alameda Naval Air station until he retired in 1988.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a member of the Veterans of Foreign Wars, Pleasant Hill Post 3059, The Mount Diablo Metal Detectors Club and the Walnut Creek Friends Church. Dave was deeply loved and will be greatly missed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is survived by his beloved wife of 58 years, Jean; sons Ron (Kimberly) of Walnut Creek, Kevin (Marti) of Concord, Richard (Kazuyo) of Hawthorne, CA, and daughter Kathleen Davis of Walnut Creek; grandchildren Leesha, Andrea, Ronnie, Cody, Kristopher, Clayton, Kiron, Brian, Justin and Alex. Preceded in death by his children Steven and Caroline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>388</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Henry Sherman Jr.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lott</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;My father, Henry Sherman Lott Jr. was in the US Navy from 1944 thru 1947. He was stationed at Alameda NAS after basic training at Great Lakes in Illinois.  His birthday was 5-3-27.  He passed 5-5-93.  He was a proud sailor.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;Provided by Mr. Hank Lott III&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>389</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Raymond John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Asmussen</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;September 9, 1928 to June 3, 2011&lt;p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Resident of San Leandro&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Beloved and devoted husband of Marjorie Asmussen, passed away on June 3rd, 2011 at the age of 82. John was born in Tacoma, Washington on September 9th, 1928. John (also known as Ray or Raymond by those who worked with him) served in the U.S. Navy for a short time and then worked as a Department of Navy civilian at the Alameda Naval Air Station for nearly 40 years, culminating his career as a Superintendent.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;John was a gentle spirit and had an enthusiastic, positive outlook on life. His influence touched many lives as he was always willing to help others and include them in his activities. John was an adventurer as well as a craftsman. He loved outdoor activities, such as camping, fishing, boating, water skiing, biking, and golfing. In his earlier adulthood, he enjoyed car rallies. His self-taught talents included stain glass design and construction. John has belonged to and held positions in such organizations as the Elks and Sons in Retirement (SIRS).&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;In addition to his wife, Marjorie, John is survived by his son Eric Asmussen, seven step-children and sixteen step-grandchildren. John is also survived by his sister, Vee Ann Baker, brother Henry Asmussen and sister-in-law Mary Lou Asmussen.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>390</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Jeanette Frances</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ayers</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/ayers-jf.jpg" width="120" height="112" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Apr. 12, 1931 to May 2, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Resident of Alameda&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jeanette peacefully passed away on May 2nd with her loving family by her side. She was born in Honey Creek, Iowa to Martin and Frances Nelson.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;She worked 30 years as a Budget Analyst at the Alameda Naval Base. Loved working on crossword puzzles, was a supporter of the Alameda Girls Club, and a member of the Alameda Hospital Auxiliary and the Soroptimist Club. Jeanette is the beloved mother to Luann (Ayers) Choy, Robert Choy (son-in-law) and loving grandmother to Kate and Amy Choy.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;She was preceded in death by her husband, Wallace T. Ayers.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>391</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Lorraine H.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cyphers</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Lorraine H. Cyphers (Harvey) Resident of Alameda Lorraine passed away peacefully on July 11, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;She is survived by her husband, Edward Harvey, granddaughter, Shannon Marsh; 2 great grandsons, Jon Marsh and Matt Marsh.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Preceded in death by her daughter, Sharon Berryman. Lorraine was born in Huron, SD.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;She moved to the Bay Area in 1943 where she found work at the Naval Air Station in Alameda, retiring after 49 years of service.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;She enjoyed cruising on the luxury liners, gambling in Reno and trailer camping. Lorraine enjoyed cooking and baking and is known especially for her zucchini bread and "South Dakota" goulash.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>392</Id>
		<Rank>CDR</Rank>
		<FirstName>George S.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gilbert</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;table&gt;
			&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gilbert-gs-4.jpg" width="300" height="91" alt="" /&gt;
			&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Small article published the local paper in Dublin. CA (The Herald, or Tri-Valley Newspaper) or the Oakland Tribune in Oakland, CA.
			&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Large article published in the Oakland Tribune in Oakland, CA by a friend or friends -- unknown to the Gilbert family as to who submitted it to be published.
			&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gilbert-gs-1.jpg" width="366" height="300" alt="" /&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;
			&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gilbert-gs-2.jpg" width="270" height="700" alt="" /&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gilbert-gs-3.jpg" width="362" height="700" alt="" /&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;/tr&gt;
			&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>393</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Claudio Molinar</FirstName>
		<LastName>Carrillo</LastName>
		<Status>Sr.</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/carrillo-cm-sr.jpg" width="168" height="244" alt="Claudio Molinar Carrillo, Sr." /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claudio Molinar Carrillo, Sr.&lt;br /&gt;June 6, 1921 - Jan. 2, 2012&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Resident of Fremont&lt;br /&gt;Born June 6, 1921 in Peoria, AZ and entered into rest on January 2, 2012 in Fremont at the age of 90. Preceded in death by his wife Sara and son Art. Beloved father of Cary and Vivian Carrillo, Sue and Fred Lopez, and Cindy Navarro. Treasured grandfather of Brian, Alicia, Carlos, Fernando, Lorraine, Pedro, Marcos, and Jacqueline. Proud great-grandfather of Aliyah, Makela, Mariah, Carlitos, Adrian, Daniel, Laneah, Cassandra, Illeana, Madison, and Mateo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On January 2, 2012 our family lost a giant of a man, a loving husband, father, grandfather, uncle, and friend to all. Tata lived a long and wonderful life and was married for 63 beautiful years to his wife and sweetheart Sara. He was a WWII combat veteran and served his country for another 30 years in the Naval Air Reserve as an Aircraft Mechanic and Flight Engineer on P-2 Navy Sub hunting aircraft. &lt;b&gt;He retired from the Naval Aviation Depot in Alameda as a supervisor.&lt;/b&gt; We are comforted to know that he is reunited with his loving wife Sara and son Art.	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>394</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Clifton</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wainright</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/wainright-c.jpg" width="194" height="194" alt="Clifton Wainwright" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			Clifton Wainwright Sept. 6, 1931 - Dec. 21, 2011&lt;br /&gt;
			Resident Of Oakland&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Clifton Wainwright was born on Sept. 6, 1931, to the union of Mitchell and Harriet Toles Wainwright in Rosedale, LA. After the death of her husband, Harriet met and married Joseph Landry who moved the family to Oakland, CA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Clifton accepted Christ at an early age and was baptized at Rose Hill Baptist Church in Rosedale, LA. After moving to Oakland, he held membership in New Hope, Havenscourt and Allen Temple Baptist churches. He enjoyed the television ministry of Dr. Fred Price for many, many years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			lifton graduated from McClymonds High School where he excelled in academics and athletics. He was the first black All City quarterback and the first black Oakland Tribune "Athlete of the Year." While at McClymonds, he met and married his high school sweetheart, Mylease Caddett. To this union were born five children: Clifford, Michelle, Mitchell, Mark and Clayton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Clifton received his Associate of Arts degree from Santa Rosa Junior College. He briefly worked at Berkeley Steel in Berkeley, CA and later was &lt;b&gt;employed at Alameda Naval Air Station as a Program Manager and a Flight Test Engineer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			He was also a member of the California Board of Realtors where he served two terms as state president, and two terms as a national president. He continued as a realtor for more than fifty years where he became an ICON.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Throughout his life, Clifton enjoyed traveling, sports activities, chess and most importantly, all relatives and friends. He will be sorely missed by all as he was noted for his great sense of humor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			He leaves to mourn his ex-wife, Mylease; one daughter, Michelle Wainwright (Dr. James) Bailey; four sons: Clifford Wainwright, DDS; Mitchell (Cecelia) Wanwright; MD; Mark Wainwright; and Clayton (Imelda) Wainwright, DDS; eleven grandchildren: Stanley Kelley, Camille Wainwright, MD, Cheryl Wainwright, MD, James Bailey, Nicole Wainwright, Jeffrey Wainwright, Marsha Wainwright, Robert Wainwright, Matthew Wainwright, Mark Clifton Wainwright, and Jennifer Wainwright; one brother-in-law, Wallace Haynes, Sr., and a host of nieces, nephews, cousins, and in-laws. He was preceded in death by his parents Mitchell Wainwright, Harriet and Joseph Landry; his sister, Anna M. Haynes; and his brother, Plandres "Joe" Wainwright.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			Clifton quietly departed this life on Dec. 21, 2011. May he rest in peace!
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>395</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gulden</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Robert "Bob" Gulden passed away on Christmas Day 2011&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Bob had many positions during his years at the base; machinist, machinist foreman, equipment specialist in Production Engineering (machine tools), and general foreman of the Machine Shop (93000 Div.) when he retired.  After retirement Bob went to work for the Viereck Company, a machine tool sales company that sold machine tools to the Government.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Bob became a mentor to me when I went to the Production Engineering Department.  Since I was put in the position that he held as buyer of machine tools, I frequently had to go and pick his brain on the complicated process of ordering the best machines for the base and how to wade through the stacks of government paperwork.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Bob was not only a good person to work with/for, he was also just a very good mild mannered person.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Russ Drake&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>397</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Louis</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lucivero</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Louis Lucivero, resident of Fremont since 1978, and prior resident of Hayward and San Leandro, passed away on November 25th at the age of 66.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Louis is survived by his wife Lorriane, daughter Laura and husband Barry of Fremont, son Louis and wife Beanie of Livermore, and four grandchildren. His sisters Lucretia, Ida, and brother Michael all of Long Island also survive him.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Louis has been a member of the Independent Order of Foresters, Italian Club, Union Local #20 of Engineers and Scientists, IFPIE vice president and past president.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Lou started as a machinist apprentice at the Brooklyn Naval Yard and when the Navy Yard closed in 1966 he transferred to Alameda.  Sometime in the seventy''s he went into the Planning Office to program NC machine tools and later CNC equipment (Bldg. 5).  He left NAS Alameda and went to United Airlines where he worked in Planning and was a negotiator for the union there.  Lou was a jolly person who always had a good joke to tell and was very easy to work with.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Russ Drake&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>398</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Dorothy T</FirstName>
		<LastName>Narahara</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/narahara-dt.jpg" width="300" height="421" alt="Dorothy T. Narahara" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			Dorothy T. Narahara&lt;br /&gt;
			May 23, 1913 – November 29, 2011&lt;br /&gt;
			Resident of Alameda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Born in Fresno to the late Kojiro and Sao Tochiura, Dorothy passed away peacefully in Alameda. Wife of the late Sam Narahara for 62 years, she raised four children: Joan Narahara, Edwin (May) Narahara, Carol (Gordon) Kono and Kenneth (Chikako) Narahara. She is survived by her beloved grandchildren: Sheryl N. (Jay) Hathaway, Craig and Neal Narahara, Kirk (Erin), Randall (Julie) and Lance Kono, and Margrethe and Kristopher Narahara. She was also a proud great grandmother of five, sister of Howard Tochiura, and was preceded in death by her sister, Irene Nakajima.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			During World War II, Dorothy and her family were interned at Topaz, Utah. She worked for 30 years at the Alameda Naval Air Station and retired as a budget analyst. She was active in numerous community organizations, including the Buddhist Women&amp;quot;s Association at the Buddhist Temple of Alameda, J-Sei, the Alameda Japanese American Citizens League, Extending Connections Seniors Program, and was a member of the National Active Retired Federal Employees.
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>399</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>LaVanya Denice</FirstName>
		<LastName>Saunders</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Beloved long-time Albany resident LaVanya Saunders, passed away peacefully in her sleep on Dec 4, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Born on Dec 21, 1951 to Moses and Etta Saunders of Oakland, CA, she attended Sacred Heart Church and School. After graduating from Emery High School she attended UC Berkeley and graduated with a BA in Social Welfare and a Master&amp;quot;s degree in Psychology. She worked for Planned Parenthood and later at Naval Air Station Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;She is survived by four siblings: DeVance Saunders Sr., Cortes Saunders Storno, Andrea Saunders and Yvette Saunders Hudson, and a community of friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Tangela Gibson&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>400</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Manny</FirstName>
		<LastName>Silvas</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Manny Silvas died on Nov. 19, 2011. He  worked at NAS Alameda back in the 1960''s to 1980''s.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;He was past District 14 VFW Commander and a NARFE Chapter 511 life member. Manny had decades of volunteering at the VA Livermore hospital and Kaiser Hayward hospital. &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Michael Wong&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>401</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Attron M</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wilson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Attron M Wilson Resident of Oakland Sept. 24, 1924 - Nov. 10, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Attron was born in Ruston, LA, and relocated to Oakland, CA, in 1943. He served his country during WWII as a Seaman First Class in the United States Navy and later worked at Alameda Naval Air Station for over 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Attron is survived by his wife of 64 years, Gladys Wilson, children, Gregory Wilson, Sandra Bethune, Jerome Wilson and Penelope Davis, 8 grandchildren and 4 great-grandchildren, 3 sisters, and 1 brother.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>402</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William G</FirstName>
		<LastName>Rose</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;William G. Rose&lt;br /&gt;
			Oct. 2, 1919 - Oct. 30, 2011&lt;br /&gt;
			Resident of Modesto&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Passed away on October 30, 2011 at the age of 92. William was preceded in death by his beloved wife of 64 years, Marie F. Rose; survived by his three children, Bill Rose (Valerie), Joyce Sherer, and Jeannie Foster; his four grandchildren, Kenneth Foster, Kurtis Sherer, Kevin Sherer, and Kerilyn Foster.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;William was a resident of Modesto, California and lived previously in Hayward, California for 20+ years.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>403</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Leroy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gallegos</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gallegos-l.jpg" width="120" height="112" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			Leroy Gallegos Jul. 13, 1952 - Oct. 14, 2011&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Resident of Oakland Leroy Gallegos was born on July 13, 1952 in Hayward, CA and unexpectedly passed away October 14, 2011 in Oakland, CA with family and friends along his bedside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Leroy was a lifelong resident of Oakland. He was a graduate of Bishop O''Dowd High School and received an AA degree from Alameda College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Leroy worked many years as a production controller at the U.S. Naval Air Station in Alameda and was later transferred to the U.S. Postal Service where he eventually retired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Leroy had a lifelong love for basketball and a love for children. He spent over twenty five years coaching basketball for the elementary kids at St. Elizabeth School. He has been the CYO (Catholic Youth Organization) athletic director for the St. Elizabeth Parish in Oakland for twenty years. He was a coach and good friend to many young people, he was a positive influence for thousands of families and that was something he enjoyed dearly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Leroy is survived by two daughters, Veronica and Erica Gallegos, his sister, Rosemary Gallegos and his brother Ted Gallegos. Leroy was preceded in death by his parents, Salvador and Trinidad Gallegos, lifelong parishioners of St. Louis Bertrand in Oakland, and by his brother, Tony Gallegos. He will be greatly missed by his grandchildren and numerous nephews and nieces he leaves behind. All his family, friends and extended family will miss his presence and his witty humor, although he will remain forever in our hearts.
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>404</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Isobel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bartels</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/bartels-i.jpg" width="120" height="112" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			Isobel Lindsay Bartels Jul. 17, 1922 - Oct. 10, 2011&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Resident of Alameda, CA Isobel Bartels, a lifelong resident of Alameda, went to be with the Lord on October 10, 2011 at the age of 89.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			A graduate of Alameda High School, Isobel "Nelson" married her high school sweetheart Vernon Bartels a year before he shipped overseas during World War II. Shortly after his return, they were blessed with two children, Jeanne and Don.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			&lt;b&gt;Isobel worked at the Alameda Naval Air Station as an executive secretary for about 20 years and then, to everybody''s surprise, she became a journeyman jet engine mechanic.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Isobel loved to travel, read, eat out, listen to music and go to movies. She enjoyed everything Scottish, was an active member of Eastern Star and loved participating in Eastern Star events. Isobel and Vernon were also enthusiastic and faithful church choir members for many years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			More than anything, Isobel cherished her family and the many friends she made throughout the years. After Vernon passed away, Isobel moved to a smaller apartment overlooking Crown Beach, then later to Water''s Edge Lodge on Bay Farm Island, and finally to Golden Care Assisted Living on Bay Farm Island.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			She leaves behind her beloved family: Her daughter Jeanne Cogan, son Don Bartels, son-in-law Ed Cogan, daughter-in-law Sharon Bartels, grandchildren Jeff Bartels and his girl friend Jen Magowan, Dave Bartels and his wife Katie, Christine Cogan-Mesa and her husband Moses Mesa, Mike Cogan and his wife Elaine and their son David Sean, Isobel''s only great-grandchild.
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>405</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Edward Bothwell</FirstName>
		<LastName>Morgan</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/morgan-eb.jpg" width="93" height="120" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			Edward Bothwell Morgan was born in Tucson, AZ on August 6, 1931 to Edward and Evelyn Morgan. The family moved to California, stopping in Columbia where his father worked as a mining engineer. His father died of black lung disease when Ed was six. His mother, Ed and older brother, Buddy "Red" Morgan moved to Albany, CA. Ed attended school in the Oakland School District and graduated from McClymonds High School in June 1948. He joined the Army in 1948 and was stationed in Germany where he met his future wife Helga. He returned to the United States and started working at the Alameda Naval Air Station. Ed established himself early in his work career as he worked his way up the ladder from a Helper General, Journeyman, Supervisor, General Foreman and finally Superintendent. Ed''s career spanned 40 years in supporting the Airborne Navy and its mission to protect our Country. Thirty-four years ago, Ed met Nancy, who later became his wife. After Ed''s retirement from the Alameda Naval Air Rework Depot, he wanted something to do to fill his free time. Ed and Nancy started a business and called it Morgan Electric &amp; Lighting in Danville. The business allowed Ed and Nancy to look for a retirement community, and they moved to Magalia. They continued their electrical business for several years here on the ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			He was preceded in death by his brother "Red" and sister Gladys.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Ed is survived by his wife Nancy of 25 years, his two children from his first marriage, son Edward C. Morgan and daughter Heidi Lisa Morgan; his grandchildren; Donnie Henriques, James and Melissa Morgan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			Ed belonged to the Alameda Superintendent''s Association, Elks, Moose Lodge, Eagles, VFW and AMVETS. He was Past President of the National Active and Retired Federal Employees (NARFE) and he was a proud Social Member of the Sons of Italy in Paradise. When Ed played good Bocce Ball, his name became Edwardo Morganinni! He will be remembered for having never met a stranger.
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>406</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Wayne</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cummings</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;My brother, Wayne Cummings, AOM2, flew out of Alameda Naval Air  Station in 1944.  He was a turret gunner in an Avenger Torpedo plane.  His plane went down in San Francisco Bay, according to the only obituary I could locate it was 23 miles off the coast.
			He and his two crew members were killed when they were on a training flight and went into a practice bombing dive and did not come out of the dive.
			I do not recall the names of the other two members, I think one was McKenzie, but I’m not sure.  My brother’s body was the only one recovered as far as I know.
			This would have happened May 22-24 of 1944.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;-- provided by Larry Cummings&lt;/i&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>407</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Joseph A.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Esposito</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/esposito-ja.jpg" width="185" height="173" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Joseph A. Esposito&lt;br /&gt;
			May 11, 1929 - Sept. 2, 2011&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
			Former Resident San Lorenzo Joseph Anthony Esposito entered into eternal rest peacefully with his family, who loved him dearly, at his bedside. 	Joe touched so many lives with his kind and gentle spirit. He was a man of grace and dignity and had a devoted faith in God.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Joe was born and raised in W. Gonshohocken, PA by his parents Francis E. Esposito and Agnes T. Esposito. Joe was a San Leandro and San Lorenzo resident
			for 50 years and then retired in Galt, CA, for the last 10 years of his life.
			Joe was a &lt;a href="http://www.legacy.com/memorial-sites/navy/?personid=153629951&amp;affiliateID=1297" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Navy&lt;/a&gt;
			veteran of &lt;a href="http://www.legacy.com/memorial-sites/ww2/?personid=153629951&amp;affiliateID=1297" target="_blank"&gt;World War II&lt;/a&gt;,
			Air Transport Squadron Two, USS Boxer CV 21. He was honorably discharged at the rank of Airman on March 20, 1950.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Joe served a long career with NARF located at the Naval Air Station in Alameda as Quality Verification Division Head.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Joe is survived by his daughters Diane Montalvo and Carolyn Lacativo, his grandchildren Angela Lacativo Greene, Darren Lacativo, Kacey Wooldridge, his great grandchildren Nathan Lacativo, Gabriel Lacativo, Sierra Greene and Gianna Greene, his sisters Nancy Brennan, Agnes Jones, Mary Dee Hopkins, numerous nieces and nephews and extended family, Maxine Esposito and stepdaughter Linda Grimoldi. Joe is preceded in death by his parents, Francis and Agnes Esposito, stepmother Rose Esposito, brother Francis Esposito and previous wife Audrey Esposito.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Joe will be remembered most for his endearing smile, passion for the game of golf, his wit and sense of humor and his unparallel love of family. Joe enjoyed camping, fixing up his home and helping his children and family members. He will be deeply missed by his daughters, family and all those that knew and loved him.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>408</Id>
		<Rank>L/Cpl</Rank>
		<FirstName>Dennis Lee</FirstName>
		<LastName>Merrill</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Dennis Lee Merrill L/Cpl  Marine Barracks   1964 NAS Vietnam 1967&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;-- provide by Sandra Gray&lt;/i&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>409</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Bertram "Gail"</FirstName>
		<LastName>Gordon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gordon-bg-roberts-ca.jpg" width="251" height="234" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Bertram "Gail" Gordon and Cora Ann Roberts Resident of Alameda&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Bertram "Gail" Gordon USMC was born in Princeton CA, July 30, 1923.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Cora Ann Roberts was born Dec. 29th, 1925 in Hartshorne, Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Gail fought his war in the grueling campaign for Guam in 1944 where he maintained Corsair fighter planes. Cora and Gail met after the war (WW2-The Big One) at the Naval Air Station in Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;They married and lived in Alameda for 58 years. Cora was a gifted seamstress and a priceless friend to all. Gail was a loyal Marine to the day he died.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Cora and Gail passed over within 3 months of each other. A memorial service was held on October 8th, 2011, at St. Joseph''s Holy Angels Cemetery, 2560 Church Lane, San Pablo, CA, 94806&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>410</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Cora Ann</FirstName>
		<LastName>Roberts</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/gordon-bg-roberts-ca.jpg" width="251" height="234" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Bertram "Gail" Gordon and Cora Ann Roberts Resident of Alameda&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Bertram "Gail" Gordon USMC was born in Princeton CA, July 30, 1923.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Cora Ann Roberts was born Dec. 29th, 1925 in Hartshorne, Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Gail fought his war in the grueling campaign for Guam in 1944 where he maintained Corsair fighter planes. Cora and Gail met after the war (WW2-The Big One) at the Naval Air Station in Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;They married and lived in Alameda for 58 years. Cora was a gifted seamstress and a priceless friend to all. Gail was a loyal Marine to the day he died.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Cora and Gail passed over within 3 months of each other. A memorial service was held on October 8th, 2011, at St. Joseph''s Holy Angels Cemetery, 2560 Church Lane, San Pablo, CA, 94806&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>411</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Ned</FirstName>
		<LastName>Alexander</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;
			&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;
			&lt;div class="bd"&gt;
			&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/alexander-n.jpg" width="120" height="112" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Ned Alexander 06/03/23 - 08/28/11&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;50 Yr. Resident of Pleasant Hill&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Survived by wife, Georgia, children, Susan, Van, Joy &amp; Warren, his beloved son-in-law: John Zubkousky &amp; seven grandchildren.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>412</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John Hamilton</FirstName>
		<LastName>Cunnyngham</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Mr. Cunnyngham is survived by his wife Doris.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;After the war he continued a career in aviation mechanics at Naval Air Station Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>413</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Thomas J.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Jones</LastName>
		<Status>Sr.</Status>
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top: 1em;"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Thomas J. Jones Sr. worked for many years as a N.A.R.F. employee in Alameda. He served in both the U.S. Navy and the U.S. Air Force, and after the war he worked there as an Aviation Metalsmith repairing airplanes.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;He also worked as a civilian for N.A.R.F. overseas, as he accepted may lengthy assignments that took him to many places.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;i&gt;--provide by his grandson Michael Mitchener&lt;/i&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>414</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName />
		<LastName />
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>415</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marilyn</FirstName>
		<LastName>York</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;div style="margin-top:1em;"&gt;&lt;div class="right-buffer"&gt;&lt;div class="polaroid"&gt;&lt;div class="bd"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/inmemory/marilyn-york.jpg" width="370" height="300" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;				&lt;p&gt;Marilyn York, the President and Co-founder of the Alameda Naval Air Museum, died at the age of 90 in her San Lorenzo home on October 4th 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;She was a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WAVES" target="_blank"&gt;Navy W.A.V.E.&lt;/a&gt; during WWII, one of the first to become a W.A.V.E. She was stationed at the Alameda Naval Air Station.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Marilyn became a "Rosie the Riveter" after the war, and spent 33 years as a Journeyman Aircraft Engine Mechanic at the Rework Facility aboard the Navy base.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;During WWII, Marilyn sold over a million dollars worth of War Bonds to aircraft and shipyard workers.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;After her retirement, she worked hard to co-found Alameda Naval Air Museum which is dedicated to the history of the Naval Air Station Alameda, Navy and U.S.M.C.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A memorial service was held on Saturday November 3rd at the Alameda Naval Air Museum.&lt;/p&gt;
			Contributions may be made In Memory of Marilyn York to the Alameda Naval Air Museum 2151 Ferry Point Rd. Alameda CA 94501 510-522-4262
			&lt;/div&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>416</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Weeks</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Robert (Bob) Weeks was a Parachute Rigger with VAW-13, and was killed in a single car accident just outside the Oakland tunnel on the Alameda side in 1967.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by his best friend Dennis Jones (an AO3 with VAW-13/VAQ-130)&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>417</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Marsha</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mezzavilla</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Born March 31, 1948 Died February 28, 2013 in Walnut Creek while in hospice.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;She had worked at Mare Island Naval Ship Yard as a sheet metal worker on the Submarines until the base closed. Then she transferred to Alameda where she worked as an Invertor specialist for NADEP until 1995.  She then got a job as a Library Media Tech in The Vallejo School District Middle &amp; High School until her passing.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Her ashes were interred in her family’s crypt in Antioch, CA. on March 15, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Malcolm Mailey&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>418</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Cleothis L.</FirstName>
		<LastName>Wilson</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Cleothis L. Wilson was born on August 1, 1932 in Arkansas. He and his family moved to Alameda when he was an infant. He attended schools in Alameda and graduated from Alameda High School.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He served in the Army National Guard and was activated into regular Army in August 1950, serving 2 years. He was then employed by the Naval Aviation Depot in Alameda as a helper, working in the same division as his father Frank. Cleo progressed through the management chain and retired as a Production Superintendent in the Engines Division, managing 600 employees. He retired in January 1988.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Of note, Cleo presented an award to his father for 40 years of service. Cleo and his father had a combined years of public service of more than 78 years.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Cleo and Melvie moved to Gardnerville, Nevada in 1993, where they enjoyed their retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Cleo departed this life on March 10, 2013. He leaves behind his wife Melvie, son Cedric Wilson, daughter Yolanda Wilkerson, son-in-law Melvin Wilkerson, stepson Arroyo Lewis, and grandsons Melvin and Marcel Wilkerson.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He will be dearly missed.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;A Veterans Service was held on Friday, March 15, at 1 o''clock at Eastside Cemetary in Minden Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Frank Nieto&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>419</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Billy Joe</FirstName>
		<LastName>Norris</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Billy Joe Norris,7/10/25 - 5/29/12&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;During WW2 in the Pacific , was stationed at NAS Alameda and other California NAS bases, including San Diego  as Air Crewman aboard a PBM 5 with VPB 19 and VPB 98 serving with pilot Lt. Arthur Harrshbarger among others, in combat areas including Eniwetok returning to NAS Alameda near the end of the war.  He helped trained pilots and crew in the use of JATO.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Wm. O. DeWitt, CASU 6  NAS Alameda WWII&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>420</Id>
		<Rank>CDR</Rank>
		<FirstName>Donald R</FirstName>
		<LastName>Oyler</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Stationed onboard USS Coral Sea, based at NAS Alameda 1970-1972.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by his daughter, Julia M Oyler&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>421</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lim</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Robert (Bob) Lim, Calibration Lab Foreman of Division 4000, NARF had passed away on January 24th, 2013.  For those who knew Bob here is only a a brief bit of info on him as his career at NARF entails much more.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Due to complications following major surgery, Bob passed away peacefully with his family at his side. Bob was in his mid seventies.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Robert had served faithfully at NARF for over 35 years.  He a former graduate from the NARF Instrument Mechanic Apprenticeship and following that served as an Instrument Mechanic in Building 400, 2nd Deck.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He was promoted Calibration Foreman to the 94330 section of the Calibration Lab. in the 3rd Deck of Bldg 400. This is  where he had spent much of his career. He was noted for his very happy disposition, congeniality and a most cooperative spirit; these attributes cause him to also be selected to serve as Division 4000''s Staff Assistant.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;One of his favorite hobbies was on the subject of Food - he would not pass the front any restaurant without studying its Menu.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He shall be missed but will always remembered as one of the Good Guys !&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Gene Quen&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>422</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>John Franklin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dierks</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;My father - John Franklin Dierks - served in the US Navy for 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He served at NAS Alameda with VR-2 as a flight engineer on the MARS from July 1952 to June 1957.  He was also part of the Ships Company VA 145 on the USS Ranger when they brought the Ranger from Norfolk, VA  - on the goodwill tour around South America - finally to home port NAS Alameda.  Dates: March 1959 to August 1961.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;I grew up in Alameda and remember when my Dad was flying the MARS from Hawaii to Alameda - couldn''t wait for him to get home as he always brought FRESH pineapple !!!&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He was born in 1920 and died in 1995.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Linda L. Dierks&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>423</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
		<LastName>Greer</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			Mr Greer worked on the 3rd deck in Building  400 at the old Alameda NAS.
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>424</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Carmine</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dinitto</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;Carmine “Dino” Dinitto passed away in Modesto on Dec. 19, 2012 at the age of 77.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;He transferred from Quonset Point to the Naval Aviation Repair Facility (NARF, later NADEP) Alameda in 1974, where he worked in Radio/Radar. After 30 years with the federal government, Dino retired in 1992.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Dino leaves behind Joy Fox, his beloved companion of 32 years, who lovingly cared for him at home in his last months.&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>425</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>Primitivo</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sonido</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details>
			&lt;p&gt;My dad worked as a aircraft mechanic for NARF for 25 years in building 40 on the f-9 fighter jets. He retired in 1970.  He passed away on Dec. 23, 1976.  He was an infantryman in the Army during WWII in the 1st Filipino Regiment stationed at camp Roberts in San Luis Obispo. Given an honorable discharge after the war and settled in Alameda got married and raised 6 children, all who still live in Alameda.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;-- provided by Ronaldo Sonido&lt;/p&gt;
		</Details>
	</Table>
	<Table>
		<Id>426</Id>
		<Rank />
		<FirstName>William</FirstName>
		<LastName>Brandon</LastName>
		<Status />
		<Link />
		<Details />
	</Table>
</NewDataSet>